Do	O
nt	O
really	O
celebrate	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
I	O
'd	O
share	O
some	O
balloons	O
.	O
24	O
years	O
young	O

Can	O
you	O
get	O
run	O
over	O
by	O
a	O
bus	O
if	O
the	O
wheels	O
fall	O
off	O
it	O
first	O
?	O

no	O
bots	O
they	O
added	O
bots	O
to	O
all	O
lobbies	O
but	O
the	O
less	O
skillful	O
players	O
get	O
more	O
than	O
pros	O

EPL	B-ORG
:	O
Allegri	B-PERSON
breaks	O
silence	O
on	O
replacing	O
Solskjaer	B-PERSON
as	O
Man	B-ORG
Utd	I-ORG
manager	O
#	O
sagagist	B-ORG

This	O
Is	O
Sad	O
!	O
See	O
Before	O
And	O
After	O
Photos	O
Of	O
A	O
Young	O
Man	O
’s	O
Shop	O
After	O
The	B-EVENT
Onitsha	I-EVENT
Fire	I-EVENT

He	O
does	O
n't	O
play	O
checkers	O
,	O
either	O
.	O
Je	O
just	O
plays	O
with	O
himself	O
.	O

Hi	O
Alyssa	B-PERSON
,	O
my	O
name	O
is	O
Dan	B-PERSON
.	O
People	O
call	O
me	O
Dan	B-PERSON
,	O
I	O
like	O
that	O
.	O
And	O
normal	O
people	O
are	O
cool	O
with	O
that	O
too	O
.	O

it	O
did	O
n't	O
.	O
Instead	O
,	O
it	O
left	O
the	O
impression	O
in	O
everyone	O
's	O
mind	O
that	O
Trump	B-PERSON
was	O
pleading	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
invoke	O
the	O
25th	O

I	O
’m 	O
off	O
acid	O
n	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
giggles	O
.	O
N	O
I	O
 ’m	O
dying	O
,	O
twt	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
segue	O
to	O
this	O
trip	O

OMG	O
!	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
run	O
a	O
mile	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
not	O
good	O
with	O
flying	O
creatures	O
!	O

Somewhat	O
affects	O
my	O
view	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
’m	O
afraid	O
and	O
I	O
’m	O
a	O
big	O
fan	O
of	O
his	O

Well	O
in	O
fairness	O
if	O
you	O
consider	O
their	O
are	O
some	O
22	O
M	O
illegals	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
US	B-GPE
that	O
's	O
only	O
$	O
2500	O
per	O
head	O
.	O

I	O
’ve	O
spent	O
my	O
whole	O
life	O
not	O
being	O
heard	O
..	O
the	O
military	O
made	O
things	O
worse	O

the	O
sky	O
this	O
morning	O
💞	O

The	B-ORG
Federal	I-ORG
Reserve	I-ORG
could	O
soon	O
pause	O
in	O
its	O
latest	O
rate-cutting	O
cycle	O
–	O
CNBC	B-ORG

Mmmmm	O
fuck	O
.	O
Already	O
came	O
this	O
morning	O
but	O
twitching	O
for	O
another	O
unload	O

#	O
worldNews	O
Brazil	B-GPE
's	O
government	O
appoints	O
economist	O
Geraldo	B-PERSON
Melo	I-PERSON
as	O
new	O
land	O
rights	O
chief	O

I	O
want	O
"	O
rise	O
and	O
shine	O
"	O
by	O
kylie	B-PERSON
 jenner	I-PERSON
for	O
my	O
alarm	O
sounds	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

can	O
u	O
just	O
take	O
ur	O
L	O
and	O
go	O
no	O
one	O
's	O
got	O
the	O
time	O
nor	O
cares	O
lmao	O

Working	O
on	O
interviewing	O
everyone	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
.	O

If	O
it	O
makes	O
you	O
feel	O
better	O
.	O
Here	O
’s 	O
me	O
about	O
to	O
fall	O
asleep	O

Always	O
choose	O
the	O
hardest	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
it	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
find	O
opponents	O
.	O
-	O
Charles	B-PERSON
De	I-PERSON
Gaulle	I-PERSON

Gee	O
that	O
’s	O
not	O
how	O
you	O
felt	O
with	O
Clinton	B-PERSON
.	O
Go	O
back	O
to	O
quoting	O
those	O
Bible	O
quotes	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
useless	O

I	O
just	O
feel	O
like	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
million	O
better	O
things	O
to	O
debate	O
about	O
besides	O
who	O
can	O
or	O
ca	O
n’t	O
say	O
the	O
N	O
word	O
..	O

Jimin	B-PERSON
just	O
ca	O
n’t	O
help	O
but	O
back	O
hug	O
Jungkook	B-PERSON
whenever	O
they	O
are	O
close	O
.	O
🤷	O
‍	O

Would	O
n’t	O
this	O
be	O
considered	O
meddling	O
in	O
forsign	O
election	O
?	O

Never	O
going	O
to	O
.	O
Kfans 	O
hate	O
one	O
half	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
softly	O
support	O
the	O
other	O
half	O
.	O
Their	O
racial	O
bias	O
shows	O
.	O

The	O
Caveman	B-PERSON
will	O
be	O
Remembered	O
–	O
Anthony	B-PERSON
Dzamefe	I-PERSON

#	O
SaveLOONA	O
do	O
n’t	O
worry	O
everyone	O
..	O
i	O
will	O
pay	O
off	O
the	O
debt	O

We	O
got	O
ta	O
cram	O
those	O
revisions	O
.	O
🙃 	O
Hahahuhu	O
.	O
Going	O
✈	O
️	O
✈	O
️	O
✈	O
️	O

I	O
present	O
for	O
your	O
notice	O
,	O
the	O
latest	O
Euro	O
deal	O
.	O

In	O
case	O
you	O
're	O
wondering	O
,	O
the	O
752	O
train	O
is	O
n't	O
here	O
yet	O
at	O
805	O
.	O
No	O
announcement	O
.	O

In	O
the	O
80s	O
,	O
I	O
owned	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
red	O
jeans	O
,	O
so	O
fuck	O
you	O
!	O

You	O
are	O
disqualified	O
from	O
offering	O
an	O
object	O
position	O
on	O
what	O
trump	B-PERSON
said	O
and	O
how	O
trump	B-PERSON
behaved	O
.	O

Also	O
!	O
Very	O
happy	O
for	O
you	O
lately	O
Jon	B-PERSON
!	O
You	O
seem	O
more	O
comfortable	O
w/	O
yourself	O
,	O
Your	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
identity	O
everyday	O
!	O

I	O
got	O
ta	O
stop	O
giving	O
people	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
doubt	O

EastEnders	B-WORK_OF_ART
spoilers	O
:	O
Tiffany	B-PERSON
confesses	O
to	O
Whitney	B-PERSON
she	O
already	O
knows	O
Leo	B-PERSON
King	I-PERSON
,	O
leaving	O
her	O
shocked	O

For	O
some	O
reason	O
I	O
keep	O
picturing	O
this	O
as	O
an	O
Eva	B-PERSON
without	O
its	O
armor	O

Jimmy	B-PERSON
johnstone	I-PERSON
was	O
a	O
wife	O
beater	O
,	O
should	O
the	O
sfa	O
remove	O
him	O
then	O

She	O
ca	O
n't	O
even	O
get	O
the	O
impeachment	O
thing	O
right	O
,	O
yet	O
we	O
're	O
supposed	O
to	O
believe	O
she	O
"	O
owned	O
"	O
President	B-PERSON
Trump	I-PERSON
?	O
🤣	O

Imagine	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
pain	O
bc	O
no	O
chaffing	O
sigh	O
it	O
"	O
a	O
dream	O
"	O

Ah	O
guys	O
mind	O
sending	O
pics	O
of	O
her	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
please	O

I	O
do	O
n’t	O
own	O
Chark	B-PRODUCT
anywhere	O
and	O
I	O
strongly	O
disagree	O
.	O

How	O
y'	O
all	O
niggas	O
be	O
wearing	O
these	O
fitted	O
shirts	O
and	O
be	O
looking	O
like	O
you	O
6	O
months	O
pregnant	O
?	O
How	O
that	O
work	O
?	O

Note	O
that	O
all	O
#	O
M23Law	O
#	O
motoringlaw	O
tweets	O
will	O
be	O
on	O
our	O
company	O
#	O
InYourDefenceLtd	O
account	O
in	O
future	O
.	O

ohh	O
okay	O
thank	O
you	O
!	O
so	O
you	O
can	O
buy	O
a	O
one	O
day	O
ticket	O
?	O

imagine	O
if	O
Stu	B-PERSON
was	O
still	O
commuting	O
to	O
Leicester	B-FAC
Square	I-FAC
😂	O

2019	O
and	O
I 	O
’m	O
still	O
upset	O
that	O
Curious	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
minute	O
long	O
😤	O

i	O
do	O
n’t	O
wanna	O
be	O
your	O
friend	O
,	O
i	O
wanna	O
kick	O
your	O
neck	O

That	O
’s	O
truuu	O
.	O
Poor	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
that	O
rich	O
and	O
visible	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
too	O
tho	O

all	O
they	O
can	O
do	O
is	O
steal	O
other	O
people	O
's	O
achievements	O
wbk	O

yes	O
me	O
too	O
sadly	O
i	O
m	O
not	O
allowed	O
to	O
have	O
animals	O
where	O
i	O
live	O
atm	O
:/	O
and	O
yeah	O
i	O
had	O
a	O
hamster	O
too	O
i	O
know	O
how	O
sad	O
it	O
is	O

Do	O
it	O
make	O
sense	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
If	O
it	O
does	O
then	O
you	O
have	O
none	O
.	O
#	O
BeHuman	O

Even	O
though	O
we	O
never	O
see	O
his	O
lips	O
.	O
Damn	O
he	O
is	O
good	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
Hahaha	O

Damn	O
it	O
walked	O
out	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
did	O
n’t	O
put	O
no	O
lotion	O
on	O
ashy	B-PERSON
sumbitch	O

My	O
answer	O
to	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
highest	O
paying	O
jobs	O
in	O
India	B-GPE
and	O
named	O
them	O
with	O
their	O
salaries	O
?	O

If	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
grasping	O
what	O
he	O
is	O
trying	O
to	O
communicate	O
then	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
here	O
you	O
are	O
just	O
lost	O

In	O
codependent	O
relationships	O
with	O
their	O
partners	O
and	O
have	O
emneshed	O
ones	O
with	O
their	O
children	O
.	O

what	O
the	O
press	O
does	O
n't	O
show	O
here	O
,	O
they	O
fail	O
to	O
show	O
that	O
neither	O
trudeua 	B-PERSON
nor	O
obama	B-PERSON
are	O
wearing	O
pants	O
!	O

PETRON	B-ORG
FOUND	O
THEIR	O
MOMENTUM	O
.	O
I	O
’m	O
gon	O
na	O
die	O
.	O
Grabe	O
this	O
game	O
🔥	O
🔥	O

Does	O
it	O
matter	O
if	O
Morrighan	B-PERSON
's	O
evil	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
As	O
long	O
as	O
she	O
does	O
n't	O
try	O
to	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O

I	O
thought	O
Turkeys	O
could	O
fly	O
they	O
’re	O
dropping	O
like	O
bags	O
of	O
wet	O
cement	O

we	O
stayin	O
overnight	O
for	O
observation	O
but	O
they	O
know	O
damn	O
well	O
i	O
’m	O
working	O
tomorrow	O
night	O
🤡	O

Lmao	O
!	O
!	O
Pelosi	B-PERSON
is	O
third	O
rate	O
but	O
a	O
first	O
class	O
fool	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

No1	O
cares	O
about	O
our	O
mental	O
health	O
unless	O
it	O
's	O
mental	O
health	O
day	O
.	O
When	O
does	O
the	O
madness	O
end	O

She	O
looks	O
white	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Just	O
because	O
you	O
have	O
0.00001	O
black	O
genes	O
does	O
n't	O
mean	O
you	O
're	O
black	O

Where	O
there	O
is	O
despair	O
,	O
Francis	B-PERSON
brings	O
in	O
the	O
witches	O

Tampa	B-GPE
woman	O
survives	O
being	O
shot	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
and	O
her	O
two	O
children	O
being	O
gunned	O
down	O
by	O
her	O
ex-husband	O

Yep	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
knackered	O
.	O
Fighting	O
with	O
monitoring	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O

These	O
next	O
few	O
months	O
have	O
got	O
potential	O
,	O
It	O
’s	O
like	O
life	O
is	O
pregnant	O

Why	O
do	O
n’t	O
17	O
year	O
old	O
guys	O
look	O
like	O
this	O
at	O
my	O
school	O
?	O
🚶	O
🏽‍	O
🚶	O
🏽‍	O

I	O
ve	O
never	O
really	O
hated	O
clowns	O
until	O
this	O
halloween	B-EVENT
.	O

I	O
like	O
the	O
early	O
court	O
sessions	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
in	O
and	O
gtf	O
out	O

Presumably	O
if	O
DUP	B-NORP
scuppers	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
become	O
the	O
baddies	O
.	O
Or	O
are	O
they	O
waiting	O
for	O
the	O
£	O
£	O
£	O
£	O
?	O

In	O
faith	O
I	O
shall	O
invest	O
for	O
the	O
Lord	B-PERSON
knows	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
's	O
desires	O
.	O
🧡	O

If	O
god	O
does	O
n't	O
exist	O
to	O
you	O
or	O
not	O
you	O
can	O
tell	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
this	O
will	O
happen	O
.	O

The	O
French	B-NORP
translation	O
was	O
painful	O
but	O
I	O
respect	O
it	O
.	O

"	O
Well	O
,	O
I	O
guess	O
being	O
a	O
hopeless	O
romantic	O
is	O
n't	O
ao	O
bad	O
after	O
all	O
.	O
How	O
fo	O
you	O
feel	O
about	O
futanari	O
,	O
sugar	O
lips?~	O
"	O

And	O
that	O
second	O
story	O
is	O
a	O
reminder	O
:	O
bitcoin	O
is	O
not	O
anonymous	O

It	O
’s	O
pretty	O
interesting	O
that	O
Tulsi	B-PERSON
has	O
so	O
many	O
Russian	B-NORP
bots	O
,	O
trolls	O
,	O
and	O
republican	B-NORP
supporters	O

Follow	O
her	O
she	O
's	O
lovely	O
and	O
humble	O
with	O
sweet	O
soul	O
😍	O
🙏	O

Asked	O
if	O
union	B-NORP
will	O
give	O
on	O
some	O
demands	O
to	O
get	O
class	O
size	O
,	O
staffing	O
,	O
Sharkey	B-PERSON
says	O
"	O
Of	O
course	O
,	O
it	O
’s	O
a	O
negotiation	O
.	O
”	O

Crushing	O
on	O
my	O
coffee	O
.	O
Because	O
people	O
are	O
unbearable	O
without	O
it	O
.	O

what	O
are	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
consequences	O
resulting	O
from	O
poor	O
girl	O
child	O
up	O
bringing	O
?	O
?	O
#	O
DayOfTheGirlChildUg19	O

About	O
to	O
make	O
myself	O
throw	O
up	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
sleep	O
😴	O
😂	O
jk	O
I	O
wish	O
lol	O

HKYF	B-ORG
is	O
the	O
best	O
and	O
great	O
eerience	O
thank	O
God	O
for	O
our	O
lives	O
💙	O

haha	O
loona	B-PERSON
do	O
n’t	O
go	O
bankrupt	O
😩	O
😩	O
🙏	O
you	O
’re	O
too	O
sexy	O
😂	O
😍	O
😩	O
🤪	O

Do	O
n't	O
you	O
have	O
some	O
🍄	O
rump	O
manure	O
to	O
eat	O
?	O
Do	O
your	O
job	O
,	O
worm	O
.	O

Looking	O
forward	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
!	O
Safe	O
travels	O
to	O
your	O
players	O
,	O
parents	O
,	O
and	O
coaches	O
.	O

lol	O
they	O
had	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
ghetto	O
when	O
i	O
fly	O
in	O
with	O
delta	B-ORG
.	O

naginodr	O
hmare	O
europe	B-GPE
me	O
Is	O
time	O
rat	O
hti	O
he	O
#	O
Paris	B-GPE

If	O
your	O
name	O
is	O
n’t	O
Woj	B-ORG
or	O
Shams	B-ORG
,	O
you	O
do	O
n’t	O
have	O
NBA	B-ORG
sources	O

It	O
feels	O
so	O
good	O
outside	O
I	O
just	O
wish	O
the	O
weather	O
was	O
consistent	O
😕	O

If	O
you	O
ca	O
nt	O
find	O
the	O
lesson	O
in	O
your	O
"	O
mistake	O
"	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
the	O
mistake	O
again	O
.	O
#	O
Reflection	O

And	O
you	O
know	O
a	O
lot	O
about	O
basement	O
and	O
secret	O
rooms	O
right	O
?	O

We	O
do	O
n't	O
have	O
the	O
Insanity	O
class	O
at	O
mine	O
but	O
I	O
totally	O
want	O
to	O
try	O
that	O

Clean	O
says	O
she	O
does	O
n’t	O
need	O
anyone	O
to	O
care	O
she	O
is	O
confident	O
in	O
knowing	O
she	O
’s	O
Taylor	B-PERSON
’s	O
best	O
song	O

Stfu	O
,	O
I	O
wear	O
all	O
three	O
(	O
four	O
actually	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
still	O
look	O
💣	O

I	O
've	O
clearly	O
missed	O
something	O
here	O
but	O
why	O
are	O
you	O
leaving	O
?	O

ugh	O
jfc	O
it	O
's	O
a	O
joke	O
,	O
i	O
was	O
n't	O
even	O
going	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
with	O
it	O
and	O
y'	O
all	O
are	O
acting	O
like	O
i	O
shot	O
someone	O

That	O
’s	O
unheard	O
of	O
.	O
We	O
ca	O
n’t	O
be	O
talking	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
TSU	O

Not	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
we	O
see	O
this	O
clip	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
haunt	O
the	O
fool	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
career	O
.	O

Thanks	O
PWD	B-ORG
for	O
replacing	O
the	O
broken	O
manhole	O
cover	O
.	O

but	O
why	O
is	O
the	O
duck	O
fighting	O
against	O
sleep	O
?	O
what	O
on	O
earth	O
is	O
more	O
important	O
than	O
a	O
duck	O
's	O
sleep	O
?	O

Ayyy	O
at	O
this	O
point	O
do	O
you	O
just	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
or	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
lying	O
lmao	O
😂	O
👀	O

2	O
exams	O
and	O
a	O
quiz	O
today	O
ladies	O
,	O
send	O
me	O
good	O
vibes	O
please	O

You	O
mad	O
sis	O
😂	O
😛	O
you	O
that	O
's	O
baby	O
stop	O
playing	O
😂	O

Man	O
found	O
dead	O
with	O
gunshot	O
wounds	O
in	O
car	O
near	O
Milan	B-GPE
-	O
English	B-NORP
-	O
#	O
dsveurope	O

A	O
happy	B-PRODUCT
meal	I-PRODUCT
.	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
'm	O
23	O
years	O
old	O
but	O
hey	O
no	O
judging	O
!	O

can	O
they	O
start	O
kcons	O
early	O
so	O
dohyon	O
can	O
join	O
the	O
ending	O
finale	O
self	O
cam	O
😢	O

Just	O
listening	O
to	O
Akon	B-PERSON
-	O
Right	B-WORK_OF_ART
Now	I-WORK_OF_ART
.	O
Goosebumps	O
.	O
Brings	O
back	O
so	O
many	O
good	O
memories	O
.	O
Take	O
me	O
back	O

Do	O
you	O
remember	O
when	O
you	O
joined	O
Twitter	B-ORG
?	O
I	O
do	O
!	O
#	O
MyTwitterAnniversary	O

That	O
’s	O
not	O
my	O
lord	O
and	O
savior	O
Jesus	B-PERSON
Christ	I-PERSON
is	O
it	O
?	O

Before	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
.	O
But	O
now	O
the	O
darkness	O
comforts	O
me	O
.	O

need	O
to	O
gym	O
and	O
need	O
to	O
study	O
for	O
my	O
nursing	O
exam	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
want	O
is	O
to	O
eat	O
some	O
bfast	O
and	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
bed	O

Tweets	O
like	O
these	O
make	O
me	O
question	O
myself	O
why	O
I	O
even	O
have	O
a	O
Twitter	B-ORG
.	O

My	O
Girlfriend	O
is	O
the	O
type	O
of	O
person	O
who	O
wants	O
to	O
name	O
all	O
new	O
pets	O
"	O
Fernando	B-PERSON
"	O

My	O
grammar	O
/	O
spelling	O
is	O
mad	O
terrible	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
🤦	O
🏾‍	O

That	O
is	O
current	O
position	O
,	O
but	O
DUP	B-NORP
objects	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
part	O
to	O
their	O
objection	O
to	O
mandatory	O
coalition	O
however	O
.	O

I	O
've	O
just	O
watched	O
episode	O
S02E04	O
of	O
Barry	B-WORK_OF_ART
!	O
#	O
tvtime	O

And	O
there	O
I	O
find	O
You	O
in	O
the	O
mystery	O
In	O
oceans	O
deep	O
💕	O

I	O
think	O
we	O
're	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
that	O
we	O
can	O
start	O
a	O
club	O
😔	O

Sender	O
's	O
email	O
is	O
info.in	O
This	O
is	O
wrong	O
on	O
so	O
many	O
levels	O
for	O
a	O
"	O
Bank	O
"	O
website	O
from	O
security	O
point	O

When	O
i	O
do	O
nothing	O
wrong	O
it	O
lets	O
me	O
know	O
people	O
question	O
sh*t	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
insecurity	O
.	O

And	O
to	O
think	O
he	O
spent	O
his	O
last	O
days	O
shamming	O
the	O
chambers	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Congress	I-ORG
by	O
joining	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
witch	O
hunt	O

Got	O
this	O
dildo	O
looking	O
thing	O
in	O
Homeroom	B-ORG
.	O
Must	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
glitch	O
so	O
I	O
just	O
killed	O
it	O
lol	O

Trying	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
bring	O
up	O
the	O
dose	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
lights	O
on	O
set	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
then	O
,	O
uh	O
.	O
then	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
men	O
.	O

meat	O
industry	O
:	O
ALSO	O
THIS	O
IS	O
ALL	O
TEENAGE	O
GIRLS	O
FAULT	O
SOMEHOW	O
.	O
TOTALLY	O
NOT	O
A	O
SEXIST	O
VIEWPOINT	O
.	O
LOL	O
WOMEN	O
ARE	O
IDIOTS	O
AND	O
VEGANS	O
.	O

what	O
is	O
this	O
start	O
eerience	O
I	O
see	O
activated	O
on	O
my	O
phone	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
sign	O
up	O
for	O
and	O
is	O
being	O
charged	O
for	O
?	O

everyone	O
cancel	O
this	O
is	O
their	O
headline	O
inexcusable	O

I	O
'm	O
raising	O
money	O
for	O
A	O
car	O
before	O
the	O
winter	O
storms	O
.	O
Click	O
to	O
Donate	O
.	O

It	O
's	O
alright	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
your	O
trying	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
annoys	O
me	O
too	O
some	O
people	O
these	O
days	O
!	O

Yesss	O
!	O
I	O
mixed	O
my	O
words	O
up	O
way	O
too	O
much	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O

Okay	O
let	O
’s	O
ignore	O
everything	O
and	O
WHAT	O
is	O
that	O
ZSS	B-ORG
fair	O

NYC	B-GPE
’s	O
Weather	O
Today	O
:	O
Pin	O
your	O
wigs	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
’m	O
gon	O
na	O
blow	O
.	O

UPDATE	O
:	O
ang	O
bagal	O
kong	O
gumawa	O
🥺	O
but	O
yeah	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
colors	O
😬	O

Shiit	O
I	O
’m	O
niggas	O
too	O
cause	O
that	O
long	O
text	O
will	O
have	O
me	O
out	O
the	O
door	O

No	O
one	O
is	O
preventing	O
you	O
from	O
creating	O
something	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
just	O
a	O
reminder	O
💁	O
‍	O
😁	O

And	O
you	O
brighten	O
up	O
mine	O
!	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
most	O
wonderful	O
day	O
!	O
💛	O
🤗	O
💛	O

I	O
did	O
n't	O
serve	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
translation	O
is	O
big	O
ugly	O
fat	O
fucking	O
yenta	O

The	O
guys	O
on	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
train	O
were	O
Brexit	B-EVENT
supporters	O
.	O

Even	O
a	O
cuck	O
like	O
yourself	O
can	O
see	O
this	O
corruption	O
,	O
huh	O
?	O

Not	O
one	O
to	O
tell	O
people	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
're	O
into	O
art	O
,	O
give	O
the	O
insta	B-ORG
a	O
follow	O

Players	O
do	O
n't	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
their	O
as	O
well	O
Kane	B-PERSON
will	O
go	O
soon	O
I	O
honestly	O
hope	O
he	O
does	O

We	O
found	O
the	O
issue	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
back	O
in	O
20	O
minutes	O
or	O
so	O
!	O

Get	O
her	O
on	O
Twitter	B-ORG
before	O
moving	O
-	O
please	O
and	O
thank	O
you	O

bart	B-PERSON
simpson	I-PERSON
rude	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
favourite	O
videos	O
i	O
do	O
n’t	O
know	O
why	O

YOU'RE	O
PATHETIC	O
AND	O
YOU	O
SHOULDN'T	O
BE	O
ALLOWED	O
AROUND	O
YOUR	O
GRANDCHILDREN	O
BECAUSE	O
YOU'RE	O
A	O
PEDOPHILE	O
SUPPORTER	O

Want	O
to	O
make	O
FREE	O
calls	O
?	O
Try	O
.	O
#	O
internationalcalls	O
#	O
internationaltexts	O

I	O
’m	O
glad	O
my	O
daughter	O
outgrew	O
that	O
song	O
,	O
it	O
’s	O
terrible	O

imagine	O
being	O
deaf	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
world	O
is	O
your	O
silent	O
study	O
area	O

Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
mind	O
.	O
Resign	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
of	O
everyone	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
up	O
to	O
this	O
job	O
at	O
all	O
.	O

So	O
sad	O
.	O
I	O
loved	O
listening	O
to	O
his	O
wisdom	O
.	O
Everything	O
about	O
him	O
just	O
made	O
sense	O
.	O
Such	O
a	O
sad	O
day	O
for	O
America	B-GPE
.	O

Lol	O
you	O
care	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
You	O
rip	O
Trump	B-PERSON
's	O
trade	O
war	O
with	O
China	B-GPE
but	O
support	O
the	O
protests	O
it	O
sparked	O
.	O
Bandwagon	O
jumpers	O

How	O
I	O
’m	O
not	O
a	O
size	O
6	O
from	O
pushing	O
this	O
fkn	O
pram	O
everywhere	O
blows	O
my	O
mind	O

Hi	O
!	O
Could	O
you	O
possibly	O
play	O
#	O
StackItUp	O
by	O
?	O
It	O
's	O
so	O
beautiful	O
!	O

So	O
like	O
them	O
skins	O
and	O
stickers	O
would	O
nt	O
have	O
an	O
owner	O
anymore	O
and	O
my	O
inventory	O
is	O
asking	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
that	O
new	O
new	O

Thanks	O
man	O
!	O
I	O
owe	O
it	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
community	O
though	O
!	O
Everyone	O
has	O
been	O
great	O
and	O
super	O
supportive	O
!	O

They	O
have	O
no	O
backbone	O
Jason	B-PERSON
.	O
They	O
’re	O
RINOs	O
and	O
are	O
afraid	O
of	O
the	O
democrats	B-NORP
.	O

Wait	O
.	O
Winter	O
in	O
the	O
northern	B-LOC
plains	I-LOC
will	O
be	O
cold	O
?	O
Dammit	O

That	O
second	O
protester	O
when	O
he	O
sees	O
what	O
’s	O
happened	O
to	O
his	O
friend	O
LOL	O

I	O
m	O
sorry	O
#	O
HarleysInHawaii	O
is	O
so	O
bad	O
.	O
I	O
tried	O
.	O
Still	O
support	O
ya	O
Katy	B-PERSON

I	O
reeeeeallllyyyyyy	O
do	O
n’t	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
10.5	O
hours	O
right	O
now	O
fml	O

What	O
do	O
I	O
want	O
for	O
Christmas	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
Columbus	B-EVENT
Day	I-EVENT
changed	O
to	O
elizabeth	B-PERSON
Warren	I-PERSON
day	O
and	O
Trump	B-PERSON
impeached	O

remember	O
how	O
i	O
struggled	O
with	O
a	O
duty	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
decided	O
blm	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
thinking	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
mch	O

This	O
is	O
the	O
third	O
vaping	O
related	O
illness	O
case	O
confirmed	O
in	O
the	O
state	O
.	O

💓	O
💓	O
it	O
rly	O
is	O
,	O
it	O
looks	O
so	O
aesthetically	O
pleasing	O
i	O
love	O
it	O

If	O
it	O
were	O
South	B-LOC
my	O
Mum	B-PERSON
would	O
have	O
sent	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
back	O
to	O
their	O
posh	O
houses	O
in	O
Surrey	B-GPE
😂	O

We	O
're	O
now	O
at	O
Deal	O
vs	O
extension	O
to	O
be	O
decided	O
on	O
Saturday	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
.	O

i	O
’ll	O
believe	O
in	O
anyone	O
who	O
is	O
n’t	O
named	O
lando	B-PERSON
norris	I-PERSON
😌	O
✊	O
🏼	O

Yoh	O
u	O
guys	O
Facebook	B-ORG
has	O
finally	O
lost	O
it	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
😅	O
😅	O
😅	O

y’	O
all	O
think	O
i	O
’m	O
joking	O
,	O
,	O
i	O
ai	O
n’t	O
joking	O
i	O
fucked	O
and	O
i	O
genuinely	O
do	O
n’t	O
know	O
if	O
i	O
got	O
charged	O
for	O
it	O

My	O
Flight	O
Rising	O
dragons	O
are	O
starving	O
they	O
need	O
food	O

Shorty	O
came	O
into	O
work	O
talking	O
her	O
ass	O
off	O
.	O
shhhhhh	O
like	O
the	O
librarian	O
said	O
everyday	O
u	O
not	O
tired	O
?	O

I	O
love	O
it	O
hereeeeee	O
🥰	O
he	O
spoils	O
tf	O
outtta	O
me	O
.	O
Anything	O
I	O
ask	O
for	O
he	O
makes	O
it	O
happen	O
.	O
🤞	O
🏽	O
💙	O
that	O
’s	O
really	O
my	O
dawg	O
.	O

If	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
nun	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
write	O
poems	O
or	O
drive	O
a	O
car	O
.	O

Yes24	B-ORG
screwed	O
up	O
my	O
order	O
and	O
sent	O
everything	O
except	O
my	O
acrylic	O
keychain	O
and	O
i	O
only	O
realised	O
it	O
ytd	O

Me	O
too	O
.	O
Show	O
of	O
the	O
tour	O
.	O
Upstaged	O
by	O
Moline	B-GPE
and	O
Milwaukee	B-GPE
#	O
thegoodland	O

.	O
please	O
look	O
at	O
my	O
applications	O
and	O
hire	O
me	O
,	O
i	O
must	O
#	O
SaveLOONA	O

Took	O
the	O
words	O
right	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
mouth	O
I	O
’m	O
calling	O
Jewls	B-PERSON
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
become	O
free	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
.	O

Boris	B-PERSON
Johnson	I-PERSON
negotiates	O
a	O
deal	O
and	O
shows	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
DUP	B-NORP
.	O

I	O
did	O
nt	O
realize	O
how	O
much	O
you	O
have	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
to	O
find	O
good	O
content	O
.	O
Thanks	O
!	O
!	O

I	O
told	O
ya	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
fussy	O
lil	O
something	O
lol	O
I	O
love	O
him	O
though	O

Joker	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
heavy	O
film	O
.	O
So	O
many	O
things	O
going	O
on	O
and	O
it	O
just	O
keeps	O
on	O
hitting	O
you	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
💯	O

Do	O
you	O
sell	O
your	O
syrup	O
for	O
folks	O
who	O
are	O
making	O
their	O
own	O
soda	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
devices	O
like	O
Soda	B-PRODUCT
Stream	I-PRODUCT
?	O

I	O
know	O
!	O
Will	O
you	O
do	O
a	O
review	O
of	O
the	O
new	O
pat	B-PERSON
McGrath	I-PERSON
holiday	O
collection	O
?	O

I	O
just	O
entered	O
the	O
drawing	O
for	O
$	O
42.50	O
tickets	O
to	O
see	O
Hadestown	B-PERSON
!	O

Listen	O
,	O
mister	O
.	O
I	O
've	O
kissed	O
Karen	B-PERSON
more	O
times	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
count	O
.	O
And	O
every	O
single	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
.	O

So	O
right	O
Pam	B-PERSON
!	O
I	O
would	O
of	O
done	O
the	O
same	O
🤷	O
🏽‍	O
♀	O
️	O
😌	O
😘	O

I	O
CSNT	O
BELIEVE	O
BTS	B-PERSON
IS	O
A	O
GEMINI	O
GROUP	O
WTF	O
.	O
CRAZY	O
WHY	O
DO	O
I	O
KEEP	O
FALLING	O
FOR	O
THE	O
GEMINISMCMSMSKSL	O

thank	O
you	O
.	O
contributed	O
to	O
the	O
action	O
via	O
crowwdfunding	B-ORG

Oh	O
you	O
got	O
a	O
car	O
👀	O
lemme	O
holla	O
at	O
you	O
real	O
quick	O
lol	O

Hi	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
fault	O
and	O
we	O
are	O
working	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
restored	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O

A890DB2D	O
:	O
Battle	O
ID	O
I	O
need	O
backup	O
!	O
Lvl	O
120	O
Metatron	O

I	O
spend	O
so	O
much	O
time	O
blocking	O
kpoop	O
Stans	O
because	O
they	O
truly	O
are	O
dumbass	O
fuckkkkkk	O

1FC7C933	O
:	O
Battle	O
ID	O
I	O
need	O
backup	O
!	O
Lvl	O
100	O
Celeste	O
Omega	O

Imagine	O
what	O
he	O
qas	O
doing	O
and	O
the	O
face	O
he	O
did	O
when	O
the	O
idea	O
materialized	O
haha	O

What	O
is	O
it	O
only	O
until	O
November	O
16th	O
because	O
I	O
just	O
wasted	O
good	O
money	O
on	O
this	O
game	O
like	O
in	O
2017	O

What	O
a	O
wonderful	O
story	O
.	O
❤	O
️	O
Handwritten	O
letters	O
hold	O
so	O
much	O
value	O
even	O
after	O
time	O
has	O
passed	O
!	O
✉	O
️	O
#	O
ThursdayThoughts	O

I	O
Woulda	O
Woke	O
You	O
Up	O
With	O
Bwa	O
But	O
Happy	O
B	O
Day	O
Hon	O
.	O
Turn	O
Up	O
!	O

If	O
i	O
know	O
you	O
was	O
gone	O
break	O
your	O
word	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O

Okay	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
moment	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
it	O
's	O
my	O
issue	O
alone	O
😂	O

if	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
ones	O
filming	O
,	O
I	O
’ll	O
be	O
ticked	O
😂	O
😂	O

Good	O
morning	O
Pepe	B-PERSON
..	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
smile	O
😆	O
Whiskey	O
Tango	O
Foxtrot	O
would	O
also	O
apply	O
😅	O

where	O
did	O
i	O
see	O
something	O
like	O
this	O
🤔	O
🤔	O
🤔	O
🤔	O
🤔	O

but	O
i	O
’m	O
okay	O
now	O
!	O
!	O
i	O
also	O
take	O
my	O
last	O
midterm	O
today	O
pretty	O
sure	O
i	O
m	O
going	O
to	O
fail	O
this	O
one	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
ok	O

I	O
killed	O
my	O
ex	O
because	O
he	O
disrespected	O
my	O
husbando	O
.	O

The	O
latest	O
Utility	B-ORG
Universe	I-ORG
!	O
Thanks	O
to	O
#	O
energy	O
#	O
climatechange	O

Brexit	B-EVENT
.	O
Soon	O
you	O
'll	O
do	O
n't	O
Trump	B-PERSON
's	O
way	O
.	O
He	O
must	O
be	O
salivating	O
knowing	O
he	O
can	O
bully	O
you	O
now	O
.	O

maybe	O
if	O
you	O
stanned	O
loona	B-PERSON
you	O
would	O
’ve	O
remembered	O
your	O
name	O

My	O
granddad	O
would	O
pushed	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
water	O
for	O
throwing	O
away	O
food	O

I	O
’m	O
almost	O
21	O
and	O
ca	O
n’t	O
picture	O
myself	O
being	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
mother	O
just	O
yet	O
.	O
how	O
can	O
teenagers	O
be	O
having	O
babies	O
like	O
it	O
’s	O
nothing	O
😭	O
😭	O
😩	O

i	O
wake	O
up	O
so	O
much	O
easier	O
knowing	O
i	O
m	O
getting	O
tattooed	O
today	O

70	O
Nail	O
Gun	O
Cartridges	O
Please	O
!	O
!	O
I	O
hate	O
Hammering	O
!	O
!	O
😡	O
😡	O
🤦	O
🔨	O
😬	O

Do	O
n’t	O
assume	O
I	O
wanna	O
be	O
on	O
your	O
priv	O
more	O
time	O
I	O
will	O
block	O
you	O

All	O
we	O
want	O
is	O
#	O
ElbarWithNewSeriesOnStarTv	O
and	O
we	O
need	O
you	O
guys	O
start	O
listening	O
to	O
us	O

real	O
men	O
tell	O
hoes	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
girlfriend	O
that	O
he	O
's	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
them	O
off	O

Tweeted	O
15	O
minutes	O
ago	O
...	O
He	O
does	O
n't	O
even	O
care	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

When	O
your	O
therapist	O
is	O
fucking	O
awesome	O
and	O
you	O
just	O
talked	O
shit	O
on	O
the	O
phone	O
for	O
30	O
minutes	O
,	O
for	O
absolutely	O
no	O
reason	O
.	O

Some	O
people	O
do	O
n’t	O
like	O
people	O
with	O
opinions	O
.	O
Strange	O
world	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
.	O
Quite	O
liked	O
Cazza	O

CATHY	B-PERSON
STOP	O
STEALING	O
MY	O
FAVORITE	O
EYE	O
THIS	O
IS	O
THE	O
THIRD	O
TIME	O
THIS	O
WEEK	O

taehyung	B-PERSON
is	O
the	O
best	O
boy	O
and	O
i	O
love	O
him	O
😞	O
😞	O
️	O

The	O
only	O
one	O
that	O
makes	O
sense	O
is	O
Talk	O
Like	O
A	O
Pirate	O
Day	O
.	O

soon	O
as	O
she	O
walked	O
up	O
she	O
would	O
’ve	O
got	O
knocked	O
tf	O
out	O
.	O
tf	O
.	O

Am	O
happy	O
that	O
my	O
parents	O
appreciate	O
the	O
video	O
I	O
made	O
for	O
them	O
❤	O
️	O
Happy	O
37th	O
Anniversarry	O
mom	O
and	O
dad	O
.	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
both	O

thank	O
you	O
for	O
holding	O
the	O
#	O
54DayNovena	O
.	O
Very	O
inspirational	O
and	O
effective	O
!	O

Had	O
a	O
dream	O
last	O
night	O
my	O
cuz	O
DTate	B-PERSON
was	O
free	O
!	O
It	O
’s	O
getting	O
closer	O
tho	O
!	O
!	O

Happy	O
birthday	O
ADB	B-PERSON
.	O
May	O
God	O
give	O
u	O
wings	O
to	O
fly	O
high	O
above	O
the	O
sky	O
.	O

Does	O
n’t	O
matter	O
who	O
and	O
why	O
,	O
I	O
just	O
decided	O
to	O
help	O
someone	O
even	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
Seo	B-PERSON
Hyunjin	I-PERSON
,	O
The	B-WORK_OF_ART
Beauty	I-WORK_OF_ART
Inside	I-WORK_OF_ART

It	O
's	O
pretty	O
good	O
stuff	O
but	O
maybe	O
we	O
're	O
biased	O
😉	O
-	O
Louise	B-PERSON

Was	O
this	O
a	O
Memphis	B-GPE
church	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
n’t	O
seen	O
the	O
video	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
about	O
it	O
lol	O

what	O
did	O
I	O
do	O
wrong	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
How	O
can	O
I	O
port	O
to	O
biko	B-GPE
😔	O

Poverty	O
is	O
n't	O
fixed	O
with	O
money	O
,	O
nor	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
wealthy	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
money	O
in	O
abundance	O
.	O

Thank	O
you	O
for	O
stopping	O
by	O
,	O
Katia	B-PERSON
!	O
😉	O
We	O
're	O
looking	O
forward	O
to	O
your	O
next	O
visit	O
!	O

Can	O
you	O
give	O
Cosmos	B-PERSON
crap	O
for	O
not	O
watching	O
trigun	O
again	O
?	O
That	O
was	O
a	O
fun	O
post	O
.	O

Rep.	O
Elijah	B-PERSON
Cummings	I-PERSON
,	O
you	O
’ll	O
be	O
missed	O
beyond	O
words.thank	O
you	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
light	O
for	O
good	O
.	O
Rest	O
In	O
Power	O

Bullies	O
Targeted	O
Me	O
For	O
Being	O
Bisexual	O
—	O
Here	O
’s	O
What	O
I	O
Wish	O
I	O
Knew	O
Then	O
When	O
I	O
c	O

My	O
thoughts	O
exactly	O
!	O
Go	O
ahead	O
and	O
pass	O
me	O
I	O
’m	O
trying	O
to	O
stay	O
as	O
far	O
behind	O
you	O
as	O
possible	O

Father	O
,	O
thank	O
You	O
for	O
being	O
the	O
God	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
love	O
you	O
Lord	B-PERSON
!	O
Good	O
night	O
.	O
😊	O

No	O
.	O
But	O
they	O
did	O
their	O
jobs	O
well	O
in	O
trying	O
circumstances	O
,	O
and	O
deserve	O
praise	O
.	O

Kaptembwo	B-NORP
mixed	O
for	O
the	O
aged	O
and	O
the	O
disabled	O
.	O
#	O
Moiheist	O
loading	O

Haha	O
,	O
Na	O
same	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
just	O
admire	O
your	O
beauty	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
thanks	O
first	O
.	O

Gimme	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
make	O
someone	O
happy	O
!	O
!	O
😁	O

I	O
promise	O
you	O
on	O
everything	O
I	O
love	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
dead	O
family	O
members	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
feeling	O
is	O
ABSOLUTELY	O
mutual	O
lmaoooo	O

y’	O
all	O
niggas	O
be	O
having	O
the	O
newest	O
shit	O
but	O
no	O
car	O
nigga	O
you	O
backwards	O
is	O
shit	O
😂	O
🥴	O

I	O
was	O
gon	O
na	O
send	O
this	O
to	O
you	O
saying	O
these	O
exact	O
words	O
💀	O

Hi	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
we	O
got	O
these	O
as	O
season	O
ticket	O
holders	O
,	O
just	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
club	O
shop	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
we	O
do	O
n't	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
correct	O
?	O

You	O
just	O
got	O
ta	O
start	O
punching	O
non	O
black	O
people	O
in	O
their	O
mouth	O
when	O
they	O
say	O
the	O
N	O
word	O
.	O
It	O
’s	O
2019	O
people	O
know	O
better	O

it	O
's	O
11:11	O
so	O
I	O
wish	O
that	O
you	O
'll	O
just	O
stop	O
being	O
bitchy	O
and	O
passive	O
aggressive	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
's	O
going	O
on	O

Watching	O
this	O
administration	O
slowly	O
fall	O
apart	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
best	O
2	O
years	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
..	O

My	O
poor	O
baby	O
just	O
throw	O
up	O
all	O
over	O
herself	O
and	O
me	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

I	O
did	O
n't	O
had	O
a	O
mental	O
breakdown	O
today	O
!	O
!	O
So	O
proud	O
self	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

My	O
mom	O
done	O
got	O
nice	O
at	O
the	O
interior	O
decorating	O
I	O
feel	O
like	O
I	O
’m	O
in	O
an	O
HGTV	B-ORG
crib	O
sometimes	O

But	O
yet	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
shit	O
and	O
#	O
pochout	O
keeps	O
trending	O
...	O

There	O
's	O
Warren	B-PERSON
,	O
Kamala	B-PERSON
,	O
AOC	B-PERSON
!	O
!	O
!	O
Trump	B-PERSON
better	O
pray	O
he	O
does	O
n't	O
encounter	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
ladies	O
!	O
!	O

Some	O
people	O
are.off	O
the	O
charts	O
.	O
Yeah	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
what	O
I	O
call	O
it	O
.	O
Off	O
the	O
chart	O
!	O
!	O

The	O
latest	O
Bioinformatics	O
Training	O
!	O
#	O
singlecell	O
#	O
genomics	O

The	O
latest	O
Freedom	B-WORK_OF_ART
of	I-WORK_OF_ART
Music	I-WORK_OF_ART
!	O
Thanks	O
to	O
#	O
percussion	O
#	O
cubase	O

The	O
latest	O
What	O
's	O
up	O
in	O
San	B-GPE
Francisco	I-GPE
!	O
Thanks	O
to	O
#	O
sanfrancisco	B-GPE
#	O
news	O

"	O
We	O
often	O
have	O
games	O
in	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
does	O
not	O
necessarily	O
mean	O
points	O
in	O
hand	O
"	O

The	O
guy	O
behind	O
you	O
:	O
"	O
Is	O
he	O
famous	O
?	O
Will	O
I	O
be	O
on	O
twitter	O
?	O
I	O
bet	O
he	O
's	O
CIA	B-ORG
.	O
"	O

Waste	O
Running	O
Down	O
the	O
Walls	O
and	O
Bugs	O
in	O
the	O
Food	O
:	O
This	O
Is	O
Animal	O
Testing	O
vía	O

Hi	O
Leonard	B-PERSON
we	O
are	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
the	O
upset	O
caused	O
.	O
Please	O
can	O
you	O
DM	O
us	O
and	O
advise	O
why	O
you	O
contacted	O
us	O
today	O
?	O

FTAs	O
only	O
really	O
work	O
if	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
major	O
erting	O
country	O
correct	O
?	O

Very	O
pretty	O
palette	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
create	O
a	O
nice	O
fall	O
look	O
.	O
The	O
pigment	O
is	O
great	O
.	O
The	O
shadows	O
are	O
a	O

Fudging	O
the	O
modifiers	O
is	O
an	O
approach	O
I	O
had	O
n't	O
considered	O
.	O
Thank	O
you	O
.	O
🥰	O

Sunflowers	O
and	O
your	O
very	O
own	O
FOX	O
!	O
Do	O
you	O
need	O
another	O
reason	O
to	O
check	O
out	O
Wild	O
Life	O
?	O
?	O
🌻	O
🦊	O

Dry	O
your	O
eyes	O
mate	O
.	O
Have	O
man	O
u	O
ever	O
been	O
this	O
far	O
off	O
us	O
after	O
eight	O
games	O
.	O
Give	O
us	O
this	O
one	O
,	O
its	O
been	O
a	O
while	O
.	O

You	O
will	O
go	O
down	O
in	O
history	O
as	O
being	O
complicit	O
to	O
this	O
criminal	O
enterprise	O
known	O
as	O
the	O
Trump	B-PERSON
presidency	O

Well	O
,	O
release	O
4	O
shows	O
and	O
the	O
terrible	O
seats	O
are	O
over	O
$	O
300	O
and	O
in	O
Boston	B-GPE
.	O
there	O
goes	O
my	O
dreams	O
😭	O

Imagine	O
in	O
2019	O
,	O
thinking	O
that	O
staying	O
in	O
the	O
UK	B-GPE
is	O
even	O
remotely	O
defensible	O
.	O

You	O
are	O
an	O
authority	O
on	O
Facts	O
?	O
!	O
That	O
's	O
funny	O
.	O

Yeeees	O
but	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
really	O
can	O
feel	O
it	O
but	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
okay	O
🤡	O
🤡	O
🤡	O

When	O
you	O
eat	O
so	O
much	O
PC	O
that	O
you	O
throw	O
up	O
all	O
over	O
your	O
shirt	O
.	O

Apologies	O
for	O
the	O
inconvenience	O
.	O
Kindly	O
send	O
us	O
a	O
DM	O
with	O
your	O
PNR	O
so	O
we	O
may	O
look	O
into	O
it	O
.	O

I	O
've	O
seen	O
this	O
50	O
times	O
and	O
it	O
still	O
gives	O
me	O
chills	O
every	O
time	O

i	O
appreciate	O
those	O
people	O
who	O
can	O
accept	O
me	O
for	O
who	O
I	O
am	O
🥰	O

Who	O
’s	O
the	O
fool	O
staying	O
up	O
until	O
midnight	O
tonight	O
to	O
watch	O
her	O
oppa	O
suffer	O
while	O
eating	O
on	O
Hot	B-PRODUCT
Ones	I-PRODUCT
?	O
THIS	O
fool	O
.	O

Third	O
rate	O
?	O
That	O
was	O
generous	O
!	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
even	O
find	O
her	O
on	O
my	O
list	O
!	O
!	O
🤣	O
🤣	O
🤣	O
🤣	O

Grind	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
lads	O
!	O
#	O
UpTheReds	O
#	O
YNWA	O

So	O
because	O
I	O
'm	O
gay	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
about	O
consent	O
and	O
kissing	O
a	O
stranger	O
.	O

It	O
was	O
at	O
nighttime	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
you	O
felt	O
ill	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
taxi	O
.	O
Ever	O
since	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
.	O
Uh	O
.	O

Morning	O
energy	O
drink	O
,	O
always	O
tell	O
someone	O
you	O
love	O
them	O

I	O
’d	O
throw	O
all	O
you	O
imbeciles	O
in	O
there	O
and	O
lock	O
the	O
exits	O

Projection	O
:	O
Not	O
right	O
upstairs	O
-	O
you	O
.	O
Total	O
Meltdown	O
-	O
you	O
everyday	O
on	O
Twitter	B-ORG
.	O
Very	O
sick	O
person	O
-	O
you	O
.	O

Posting	O
this	O
once	O
in	O
awhile	O
but	O
y’	O
all	O
have	O
to	O
agree	O
I	O
’m	O
both	O
handsome	O
and	O
pretty	O

Not	O
the	O
most	O
"	O
filtered	O
"	O
President	B-PERSON
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
something	O
he	O
's	O
not	O
...	O
GOOD	O
!	O
I	O
like	O
it	O
..	O
!	O
!	O

It	O
's	O
hard	O
to	O
find	O
joy	O
when	O
holding	O
hands	O
is	O
banned	O
.	O

What	O
is	O
need	O
of	O
advertising	O
on	O
tweeter	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
do	O
n't	O
impose	O
on	O
people	O

How	O
is	O
my	O
professor	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
0	O
%	O
on	O
an	O
assignment	O
that	O
’s	O
due	O
IN	O
TWO	O
DAYSSSSSSS	O
!	O

How	O
can	O
miners	O
move	O
up	O
the	O
#	O
AI	O
and	O
#	O
analytics	O
maturity	O
ladder	O
?	O
#	O
TTT2019	O
reveals	O
where	O
companies	O
can	O
invest	O
:	O

Like	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
was	O
different	O
lmao	O
from	O
any	O
other	O
artist	O
I	O
done	O
seen	O
bitch	O
I	O
need	O
him	O
one	O
time	O
.	O

Bros.	O
The	O
resemblance	O
is	O
uncanny	O
.	O
Wonder	O
if	O
Obama	B-PERSON
also	O
has	O
a	O
Cuban	B-NORP
relative	O

Not	O
knocking	O
life	O
insurance	O
.	O
Just	O
saying	O
be	O
wise	O
about	O
it	O
.	O

"	O
Missing	O
yaya	O
daily	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
who	O
do	O
n’t	O
make	O
me	O
feel	O
basic	O
!	O
”	O
...	O
talk	O
your	O
shit	O
YB	O

This	O
was	O
my	O
first	O
and	O
only	O
.	O
I	O
’ll	O
go	O
back	O
up	O
in	O
June	O
and	O
see	O
family	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
folks	O
,	O
hopefully	O
get	O
to	O
The	O
Stadium	O
.	O

You	O
're	O
either	O
overestimating	O
me	O
or	O
you	O
're	O
downgrading	O
ma	O
man	O
Hasan	B-PERSON
😂	O

Me	O
when	O
i	O
see	O
another	O
girl	O
talk	O
to	O
my	O
boii	O
.	O
Siap	O
kau	O
!	O
!	O

Look	O
at	O
the	O
Farage	B-PERSON
,	O
sorry	O
,	O
Brexit	B-NORP
Party	I-NORP
fading	O
away	O
.	O
Time	O
to	O
resign	O
again	O
Nigel	B-PERSON
.	O

Hi	O
.	O
You	O
'd	O
need	O
to	O
visit	O
your	O
nearest	O
Vodacom	B-ORG
Store	I-ORG
to	O
find	O
out	O
.	O

Eight	O
presidential	O
candidates	O
have	O
already	O
qualified	O
for	O
the	O
November	O
debate	O
.	O
Enough	O
.	O
via	O

He	O
conceded	O
to	O
the	O
EU	B-ORG
on	O
every	O
point	O
.	O
He	O
’s	O
negotiated	O
nothing	O
new	O
.	O

Accurate	O
!	O
That	O
's	O
why	O
I	O
decided	O
to	O
deactivate	O
and	O
uninstall	O
my	O
fb	O
.	O
Soon	O
lahi	O
nasad	O
nga	O
account	O

With	O
your	O
head	O
in	O
the	O
clouds	O
,	O
nobody	O
wants	O
you	O
No-one’s	O
wasting	O
their	O
time	O
caring	O
about	O
you	O

Was	O
definitely	O
weather	O
fit	O
for	O
a	O
duck	O
but	O
the	O
smiles	O
and	O
hard	O
work	O
were	O
worth	O
braving	O
the	O
elements	O
.	O

i	O
genuinely	O
missed	O
this	O
.	O
the	O
fancams	O
,	O
airport	O
photos	O
,	O
speculations	O
on	O
new	O
releases	O
,	O
,	O
,	O
nostalgic	O
;	O
-	O
;	O
glad	O
to	O
be	O
back	O
.	O

Exactly	O
what	O
the	O
EU	B-ORG
should	O
do	O
No	O
more	O
games	O
and	O
pointless	O
delays	O
.	O
Clear	O
option	O
support	O
this	O
or	O
we	O
just	O
leave	O
.	O

That	O
's	O
an	O
Bloody	O
Amy	B-PERSON
Adams	I-PERSON
!	O
Do	O
n't	O
worry	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
throw	O
my	O
slippers	O
at	O
it	O
!	O

Slept	O
through	O
my	O
gp	O
appointment	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
train	O
for	O
my	O
night	O
out	O
and	O
I	O
still	O
have	O
the	O
cold	O
.	O
Nightshift	O
is	O
the	O
devil	O
😭	O

Y	O
’all	O
,	O
she	O
even	O
did	O
a	O
fake	O
freak	O
out	O
😂	O
"	O
OH	O
oH	O
mY	O
GoSh	O
wHat	O
hAppEnNed	O
”	O
😂	O

not	O
to	O
be	O
that	O
guy	O
but	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
put	O
flowers	O
in	O
his	O
hair	O

See	O
what	O
I	O
mean	O
.	O
Like	O
why	O
is	O
tank	O
tapped	O
in	O
lmaooo	O
.	O

Maaaaan	O
,	O
I	O
’m	O
just	O
tryna	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
bleach	O
my	O
hair	O
and	O
eat	O
some	O
grilled	O
cheese	O

Lol	O
that	O
’s	O
exactly	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
saying	O
.	O
And	O
those	O
rear	O
feet	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
air	O
.	O
I	O
love	O
it	O
!	O
😆	O
🤣	O

They	O
could	O
and	O
should	O
denaturalize	O
Seb	B-PERSON
Gorka	I-PERSON
for	O
lying	O
on	O
his	O
application	O
.	O

Wow	O
i	O
m	O
finally	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
part	O
where	O
Dimitri	B-PERSON
stops	O
being	O
mean	O
and	O
loves	O
me	O
back	O

My	O
sister	O
got	O
kicked	O
out	O
of	O
class	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
for	O
speaking	O
Spanish	B-NORP

It	O
more	O
likely	O
they	O
’re	O
thinking	O
"	O
why	O
do	O
have	O
to	O
listen	O
to	O
this	O
moron	O
speak	O
”	O

🤣	O
🤣	O
😂	O
Should	O
have	O
known	O
really	O
it	O
was	O
right	O
outside	O
the	O
swimming	O
baths	O
🤣	O
😂	O

Wait	O
until	O
they	O
find	O
out	O
what	O
Carbon	O
Neutral	O
2050	O
actually	O
means	O
..	O

I	O
think	O
about	O
you	O
every	O
night	O
You	O
're	O
everything	O
That	O
can	O
ruin	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
try	O

Looks	O
better	O
then	O
the	O
cape	O
imo	O
but	O
it	O
’s	O
good	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
an	O
option	O
to	O
get	O
both	O
but	O
I	O
recommend	O
the	O
shield	O
tbh	O
👀	O

I	O
really	O
need	O
to	O
protect	O
my	O
tweets	O
is	O
there	O
no	O
option	O
but	O
delete	O
?	O

Ahaha	O
Trump	B-PERSON
ignores	O
Cummings	B-PERSON
death	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
should	O
-	O
I	O
Love	O
this	O
President	B-PERSON

this	O
is	O
a	O
lawsuit	O
about	O
them	O
not	O
doing	O
a	O
sponsor	O
as	O
a	O
whole	O
group	O
asdhfsgfg	O
they	O
just	O
sent	O
yeojin	B-PERSON

I	O
personally	O
hate	O
it	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
not	O
cover	O
them	O
?	O
Like	O
a	O
paint	O
or	O
binding	O
layer	O
on	O
top	O
not	O
using	O
3D	O
fibre	O
.	O

Follow	O
me	O
and	O
everyone	O
who	O
retweets	O
,	O
likes	O
this	O
and	O
comments	O
IFB	O
⚱	O
️	O
🍻	O
🍫	O

#	O
IKnowItsTroubleWhen	O
the	O
reply	O
text	O
is	O
just	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
k	O

It	O
was	O
me	O
.	O
i	O
ate	O
my	O
lunch	O
sandwich	O
at	O
10	O
as	O
a	O
snack	O
.	O

people	O
who	O
support	O
rapists	O
do	O
n’t	O
deserve	O
that	O
kinda	O
money	O

If	O
you	O
read	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
timeline	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
see	O
that	O
the	O
real	O
Bill	B-PERSON
O'Reilly	I-PERSON
is	O
still	O
there	O
.	O

Dear	O
summer	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
all	O
these	O
ppl	O
were	O
being	O
mean	O
to	O
you	O
but	O
I	O
really	O
liked	O
having	O
you	O
around	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
you	O
already	O
.	O
See	O
you	O
next	O
year	O
.	O
✌	O
🏽	O

Since	O
I	O
ve	O
been	O
riding	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
dipped	O
down	O
to	O
about	O
50	O
somethin	O
a	O
couple	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
m	O
straight	O
on	O
that	O
.	O

I	O
’m	O
trying	O
but	O
this	O
shit	O
does	O
n’t	O
want	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
be	O
great	O

If	O
blacks	O
had	O
their	O
own	O
planet	O
then	O
we	O
would	O
be	O
suffering	O
Space	O
invaders	O

Use	O
it	O
when	O
cooking	O
beans	O
,	O
anything	O
you	O
need	O
to	O
fry	O
real	O
quick	O
,	O
cabbage	O
,	O
seasoning	O
a	O
cast	O
iron	O
skillet	O
.	O

Greta	B-PERSON
has	O
TDS	O
.	O
She	O
should	O
be	O
in	O
hospital	O
bed	O
somewhere	O
,	O
not	O
on	O
television	O
.	O

I	O
would	O
've	O
been	O
PISSED	O
to	O
the	O
highest	O
level	O
of	O
pisstivity	O
🤬	O

"	O
I	O
married	O
jimin	B-PERSON
because	O
I	O
'm	O
awesome	O
"	O
Why	O
..	O
yes	O
😏	O

Please	O
read	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
The	B-PERSON
President	I-PERSON
is	O
waiting	O
for	O
your	O
answer	O
.	O

everyone	O
turning	O
into	O
a	O
furry	O
bc	O
of	O
that	O
one	O
show	O
LOL	O

Elain	B-PERSON
this	O
and	O
what	O
Omar	B-PERSON
is	O
doing	O
to	O
make	O
changes	O
in	O
her	O
district	O
🦗	O
🦗	O

I	O
hope	O
that	O
if	O
you	O
break	O
the	O
EU	B-ORG
deal	O
on	O
Saturday	O
you	O
as	O
a	O
party	O
will	O
be	O
handing	O
back	O
the	O
billion	O
pound	O
to	O
the	O
UK	B-NORP
government	I-NORP

he	O
looks	O
like	O
he	O
’s	O
crying	O
🥺	O
✋	O
🏽	O
he	O
’s	O
so	O
baby	O
🥺	O
🥺	O
🥺	O
🥺	O
🥺	O

Are	O
you	O
proud	O
of	O
pandering	O
to	O
Putin	B-PERSON
?	O
?	O
Are	O
you	O
trying	O
to	O
offer	O
Europe	B-GPE
to	O
Putin	B-PERSON
?	O
?	O

For	O
Mike	B-PERSON
:	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
biggest	O
challenge	O
to	O
make	O
Doctor	O
Sleep	O
?	O

If	O
your	O
main	O
takeaway	O
from	O
this	O
movie	O
is	O
"	O
the	O
de-ageing	O
did	O
n't	O
completely	O
convince	O
me	O
"	O
then	O
I	O
suspect	O
The	O
Irishman	B-NORP
is	O
not	O
for	O
you	O
.	O

God	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
fly	O
on	O
the	O
wall	O
during	O
that	O
meeting	O
🤣	O
🤣	O
🤣	O

You	O
are	O
still	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
realest	O
people	O
on	O
twitter	B-ORG

Stunning	O
3	O
Double	O
rooms	O
in	O
end	O
terrace	O
house	O
London	B-GPE

How	O
can	O
people	O
stand	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
sun	O
on	O
your	O
bare	O
skin	O
?	O

😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
just	O
being	O
realistic	O
coz	O
you	O
never	O
know	O
what	O
these	O
brands	O
want	O
😊	O
😊	O

Would	O
we	O
be	O
living	O
in	O
Camden	B-GPE
?	O
Getting	O
a	O
ticket	O
to	O
your	O
band	O
?	O
#	O
Daydreaming	O

"	O
You	O
not	O
even	O
black	O
you	O
probably	O
African	B-NORP
of	O
some	O
shit	O
"	O
?	O
😂	O
😭	O
😭	O
🤣	O

Let	O
's	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
suggesting	O
that	O
no	O
one	O
will	O
write	O
to	O
the	O
Palace	B-ORG
?	O

Girl	O
Youn	O
know	O
if	O
you	O
wanna	O
sleep	O
,	O
eat	O
,	O
shit	O
or	O
cry	O
😂	O
but	O
whatever	O
you	O
with	O
I	O
’m	O
behind	O
ya	O
💯	O
x	O

I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
in	O
astrology	O
but	O
astrocafe	B-ORG
has	O
definitely	O
peaked	O
my	O
interest	O
.	O

HEEHEEHEE	O
.	O
i	O
wo	O
nt	O
push	O
my	O
luck	O
...	O
thank	O
you	O
anne	O
for	O
encouraging	O
me	O
when	O
it	O
counts	O

Now	O
that	O
's	O
practical	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
does	O
it	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
him	O
a	O
schmuck	O
just	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
goat	O
.	O
😂	O

Next	O
year	O
!	O
!	O
Linda	B-PERSON
is	O
a	O
good	O
navigator	O
maybe	O
I	O
can	O
find	O
them	O
next	O
summer	O
.	O

😺	O
tbh	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
cheap	O
like	O
$	O
40	O
for	O
pretty	O
decent	O
seats	O

Wow	O
Ben	B-PERSON
really	O
owned	O
the	O
libs	B-NORP
with	O
facts	O
and	O
logic	O
on	O
this	O
one	O
.	O

Can	O
I	O
watch	O
Naruto	B-PERSON
and	O
skip	O
the	O
fillers	O
or	O
do	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
watch	O
them	O
too	O
?	O

I	O
’m	O
telling	O
you	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
😂	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
world	O
record	O
sprint	O
too	O
!	O

It	O
’s	O
almost	O
as	O
if	O
y’	O
all	O
do	O
n’t	O
know	O
this	O
album	O
exists	O
?	O

Well	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
Trump	B-PERSON
is	O
going	O
to	O
unleash	O
his	O
wrath	O
on	O
you	O
Marco	B-PERSON
.	O
But	O
,	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
praising	O
!	O

Exactly	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
nibble	O
on	O
fruits	O
,	O
Veg	O
.	O
but	O
not	O
a	O
full	O
meal	O
.	O

Sad	O
loss	O
for	O
not	O
only	O
Baltimore	B-GPE
,	O
but	O
our	O
whole	O
country	O
.	O

see	O
that	O
’s	O
why	O
i	O
ca	O
n’t	O
stand	O
this	O
acc	O
,	O
y’	O
all	O
are	O
just	O
ignorant	O
on	O
here	O

Hey	O
!	O
Check	O
out	O
Gabes	B-ORG
I	O
've	O
gotten	O
2	O
really	O
nice	O
Carharts	B-ORG
for	O
$	O
40	O
!	O

That	O
’s	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
business	O
though	O
🤷	O
🏾‍	O
sucks	O
to	O
suck	O

She	O
has	O
plans	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
NG	B-GPE
.	O
I	O
guess	O
they	O
can	O
afford	O
her	O
after	O
all	O
😭	O

ooooh	O
...	O
sis	O
...	O
rip	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
we	O
will	O
miss	O
you	O
and	O
remember	O
you	O
aside	O
from	O
this	O
.	O

That	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
#	O
PelosiMeltdown	O
..	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
#	O
SmackDown	O
and	O
she	O
’s	O
only	O
begun	O
!	O
!	O
#	O
IstandwithPelosi	O

the	O
final	O
was	O
amazing	O
it	O
give	O
me	O
chill	O
.	O
CANT	O
WAIT	O
FOR	O
SEASON	O
2	O

Buddy	B-ORG
Pyramid	I-ORG
bitch	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
what	O
the	O
$	O
1	O
bill	O
for	O
😈	O
#	O
BP	O

Finally	O
Essa	B-PERSON
dragged	O
him	O
down	O
the	O
drain	O
😄	O
y	O
metina	O
deh	O
...	O

I	O
absolutely	O
am	O
in	O
love	O
with	O
her	O
she	O
’s	O
so	O
in	O
someone	O
great	O
and	O
Jane	B-WORK_OF_ART
the	I-WORK_OF_ART
virgin	I-WORK_OF_ART
ughhhh	O

Lmfaoo	O
I	O
’ll	O
be	O
there	O
at	O
10:30	O
-	O
11	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
stop	O
at	O
work	O
to	O
help	O
out	O

I	O
've	O
just	O
posted	O
a	O
new	O
blog	O
:	O
Sarah	B-PERSON
Ofili	I-PERSON
welcomes	O
baby	O
girl	O
,	O
shares	O
maternity	O
photo	O

Wow	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
how	O
ineffective	O
our	O
President	B-PERSON
is	O
👍	O
🏼	O
#	O
MAGA	O

It	O
's	O
the	O
fecking	O
proxmity	O
to	O
the	O
Dubs	O
has	O
be	O
gone	O
this	O
way	O
.	O

Yeah	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
recurring	O
dreams	O
about	O
bad	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
good	O
dreams	O
too	O
!	O

i	O
love	O
losing	O
followers	O
because	O
i	O
'm	O
retweeting	O
furry	O
stuff	O
and	O
y'	O
all	O
ca	O
n't	O
take	O
it	O
.	O

Seeing	O
wanting	O
to	O
collaborate	O
with	O
and	O
you	O
guys	O
need	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
happen	O
🤘	O
🏻	O

college	O
is	O
"	O
mahuman	O
lang	O
ni	O
nga	O
week	O
"	O
and	O
that	O
week	O
continues	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
4	O
years	O
🙂	O
🙂	O
🙂	O

Have	O
fun	O
with	O
KCD	B-ORG
aka	O
"	O
Accidentally	O
Murder	O
People	O
in	O
their	O
Sleep	O
"	O
Simulator	O
.	O
Great	O
game	O
but	O
tough	O
at	O
the	O
start	O

you	O
're	O
right	O
and	O
we	O
ca	O
n't	O
do	O
anything	O
about	O
that	O
.	O
🤯	O

What	O
it	O
looks	O
like	O
taking	O
the	O
moral	O
high	O
road	O
vs	O
how	O
streamer	O
twitter	B-ORG
sees	O
themselves	O
taking	O
the	O
high	O
road	O

Hey	O
can	O
you	O
play	O
"	O
Hot	B-WORK_OF_ART
Girl	I-WORK_OF_ART
Summer	I-WORK_OF_ART
"	O
by	O
Megan	B-PERSON
,	O
I	O
love	O
this	O
song	O
so	O
much	O
!	O

mine	O
came	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
s'end	O
.	O
currently	O
on	O
.	O

All	O
the	O
“	O
present	O
”	O
votes	O
are	O
so	O
cowardly	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
they	O
pay	O
dearly	O
at	O
the	O
polls	O
.	O

Ahhh	O
😂	O
he	O
look	O
like	O
them	O
myplayers	O
with	O
the	O
scuffed	O
facescan	O
from	O
2k16	O
wit	O
the	O
scrunched	O
up	O
faces	O

We	O
're	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
,	O
Jack	B-PERSON
!	O
Thanks	O
for	O
helping	O
us	O
celebrate	O
#	O
McRibSZN	O
!	O

She	O
can	O
ride	O
me	O
any	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
,	O
with	O
ha	O
fine	O
ass	O

She	O
is	O
not	O
Mexican	B-NORP
👏	O
🏼	O
👏	O
🏼	O
👏	O
🏼	O
👏	O
🏼	O
she	O
is	O
Puerto	B-NORP
rican	I-NORP
!	O
👏	O
🏼	O
👏	O
🏼	O
👏	O
🏼	O

Obama	B-PERSON
did	O
n’t	O
start	O
the	O
war	O
,	O
W	O
did	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Republican	B-NORP
controlled	O
house	B-ORG
and	O
senate	B-ORG
.	O

Tbh	O
I	O
have	O
n’t	O
listened	O
to	O
music	O
in	O
English	B-NORP
in	O
like	O
2	O
weeks	O

Is	O
that	O
something	O
found	O
in	O
English	B-NORP
class	O
or	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
for	O
that	O
one	O
?	O

wish	O
i	O
used	O
this	O
app	O
more	O
but	O
i	O
’m	O
genuinely	O
never	O
free	O

Stop	O
I	O
know	O
😳	O
turns	O
me	O
off	O
online	O
shopping	O
all	O
together	O

I	O
watched	O
the	O
first	O
season	O
on	O
netflix	B-ORG
and	O
then	O
when	O
S2	O
dropped	O
I	O
used	O
a	O
streaming	O
site	O

You	O
can	O
inject	O
those	O
protesters	O
getting	O
beat	O
up	O
at	O
Canning	B-FAC
Town	I-FAC
station	I-FAC
into	O
my	O
veins	O
,	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
middle	O
class	O
nonsense	O
is	O
that	O

You	O
are	O
absolutely	O
correct	O
John	B-PERSON
.	O
Vietnam	B-EVENT
was	O
never	O
a	O
declared	O
War	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
a	O
shithole	O
that	O
cost	O
58000	O
American	B-NORP
Lives	O
.	O

No	O
point	O
going	O
to	O
James	B-PERSON
Arthur	I-PERSON
Saturday	O
just	O
saw	O
every	O
second	O
on	O
someone	O
's	O
Snapchat	B-ORG

Only	O
a	O
French	B-NORP
would	O
write	O
that	O
!	O
(	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
french	B-NORP
)	O
🤣	O

The	O
German	B-NORP
is	O
adamant	O
he	O
has	O
n't	O
downed	O
tools	O
since	O
signing	O
a	O
bumper	O
£	O
350,000-a	O
-	O
week	O
deal	O
at	O
the	O
Emirates	B-FAC

Australian	B-NORP
Dollars	O
.	O
The	O
one	O
that	O
gives	O
you	O
60	O
jewels	O
instead	O
of	O
30	O
jewels	O
by	O
doing	O
daily	O
missions	O
/	O
quests	O

Well	O
...	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
idea	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
the	O
jealous	O
type	O
.	O

California	B-GPE
's	O
big	O
July	O
quakes	O
strain	O
major	O
fault	O

Till	O
then	O
lots	O
of	O
talk	O
about	O
what	O
we	O
offer	O
up	O
for	O
Henry	B-PERSON
as	O
Melbourne	B-GPE
also	O
after	O
him	O
😖	O
😖	O

Frankfurt	B-GPE
fan	O
scene	O
:	O
"	O
No	O
further	O
words	O
"	O
about	O
UEFA	B-ORG

Lmao	O
here	O
comes	O
the	O
sand	O
box	O
vet	O
to	O
defend	O
Russia	B-GPE
’s	O
interests	O

The	O
North	B-GPE
Korea	I-GPE
of	O
US	B-GPE
News	O
.	O
Check	O
out	O
the	O
bar	O
graphs	O
.	O
They	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
set	O
it	O
...	O
highest	O
to	O
lowest	O
.	O
😀	O

I	O
’m	O
waiting	O
for	O
Putin	B-PERSON
to	O
tell	O
Donald	B-PERSON
they	O
need	O
Alaska	B-GPE
back	O
.	O

I	O
'm	O
at	O
Clapham	B-GPE
now	O
...	O
No	O
sign	O
of	O
any	O
heating	O
and	O
I	O
'm	O
sitting	O
right	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
grille	O

Patriots	B-ORG
'	O
Rumor	O
:	O
Team	O
inquired	O
about	O
availability	O
of	O
Broncos	B-ORG
'	O
wideout	O
Emmanuel	B-PERSON
Sanders	I-PERSON

A	O
massive	O
money-laundering	O
scandal	O
stains	O
the	O
image	O
of	O
Nordic	B-NORP
banks	O
#	O
LiveIndex	O

What	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
a	O
muslim	B-NORP
Orthopedic	O
surgeon	O
?	O

All	O
Scandinavian	B-NORP
countries	O
except	O
their	O
migrant	O
muslim	B-NORP
population	O
are	O
the	O
most	O
forward	O
in	O
the	O
world	O

Mexican	B-NORP
security	O
forces	O
free	O
El	B-PERSON
Chapo	B-PERSON
's	O
son	O
to	O
protect	O
lives	O
:	O
minister	O

Do	O
you	O
think	O
Kanye	B-PERSON
has	O
a	O
chance	O
of	O
better	O
a	O
Republican	B-NORP
nominee	O
for	O
2024	O
?	O

Lol	O
...	O
House	B-ORG
democrats	B-NORP
trying	O
to	O
get	O
trump	O
only	O
uncover	O
democrat	B-NORP
corruption	O
...	O

micheal	B-PERSON
sheen	I-PERSON
and	O
i	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
busted	O
big	O
time	O
for	O
what	O
tho	O
?	O

Why	O
legendary	O
Mount	B-LOC
Timpanogos	I-LOC
is	O
Utah	B-GPE
's	O
'	O
Everest	B-LOC
'	O

I	O
’d	O
love	O
to	O
delete	O
my	O
Facebook	B-ORG
account	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
miss	O
the	O
private	O
groups	O
.	O
Discord	B-ORG
could	O
replace	O
that	O
I	O
guess	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
as	O
easily	O
.	O

'	O
Barbaric	O
'	O
tests	O
on	O
monkeys	O
lead	O
to	O
calls	O
for	O
closure	O
of	O
German	B-NORP
lab	O

Hope	O
chinese	B-NORP
nation	O
can	O
use	O
Twitter	B-ORG
the	O
way	O
you	O
can	O
...	O
So	O
they	O
too	O
can	O
spread	O
voice	O
of	O
China	B-GPE
to	O
the	O
world	O

hiking	O
in	O
yosemite	B-LOC
is	O
by	O
far	O
the	O
best	O
thing	O
i	O
ve	O
ever	O
done	O

Rushmore	B-LOC
is	O
not	O
that	O
big	O
...	O

BREAKING	O
NEWS	O
!	O
Barcelona	B-ORG
vs	O
Real	B-ORG
Madrid	I-ORG
Match	O
Has	O
Been	O
Postponed	O

your	O
game	O
borderlands	B-PRODUCT
3	I-PRODUCT
just	O
burned	O
out	O
my	O
PS4	B-PRODUCT
pro	O
I	O
want	O
something	O
done	O
about	O
this	O

Nigga	O
I	O
’m	O
traumatized	O
when	O
I	O
walked	O
out	O
the	O
train	O
station	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
umbrella	O
ready	O
.	O

How	O
Unity	B-ORG
built	O
the	O
world	O
’s	O
most	O
popular	O
game	O
engine	O
?	O

While	O
we	O
training	O
hard	O
for	O
the	O
awaited	O
match	O
,	O
Liverpool	B-ORG
is	O
playing	O
basketball	O
🙄	O

Damn	O
I	O
thought	O
for	O
a	O
second	O
this	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
game	O
to	O
be	O
re-released	O
😢	O
miniatures	O
are	O
cool	O
too	O
though	O
😊	O

The	O
shoe	O
industry	O
is	O
at	O
war	O
with	O
itself	O
over	O
stolen	O
design	O

Fuming	O
we	O
’re	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Rodgers	B-PERSON
/	O
Mahomes	B-PERSON
match	O
up	O
.	O

Van	B-PERSON
Dijk	I-PERSON
:	O
Man	B-ORG
Utd	I-ORG
clash	O
is	O
not	O
Liverpool	B-ORG
's	O
biggest	O
match	O

Jim	B-PERSON
McCormick	I-PERSON
had	O
the	O
6th	O
greatest	O
peak	O
in	O
baseball	O
history	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
WAR	B-ORG
.	O
#	O
McCormick4HOF	O

Come	O
and	O
Visit	O
Our	O
Cutie	O
Store	O
❤	O
️	O
1215	O
Taft	B-FAC
Highway	I-FAC
,	O
Signal	B-GPE
Mountain	I-GPE
,	O
TN	B-GPE

My	O
car	O
is	O
literally	O
going	O
5	O
mph	O
on	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
ppl	O
are	O
honking	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
’m	O
hella	O
late	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
yalls	O
morning	O
?	O

If	O
you	O
’re	O
leaving	O
a	O
playoff	O
game	O
before	O
it	O
’s	O
over	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
a	O
“	O
fan	O
”	O
.	O

I	O
found	O
the	O
Caretaker	B-PRODUCT
game	O
coming	O
out	O
on	O
XBox	B-PRODUCT
-	O
funny	O
that	O
I	O
’m	O
getting	O
key	O
requests	O
for	O
it	O

'	O
TOO	O
LATE	O
'	O
,	O
SHE	O
CRIED	O
,	O
AS	O
SHE	O
WAVED	O
HER	O
WOODEN	O
LEG	O
#	O
auspol	O

It	O
’s	O
not	O
just	O
a	O
GAME	O
DAY	O
.....	O
it	O
’s	O
a	B-EVENT
CONFERENCE	I-EVENT
CHAMPIONSHIP	I-EVENT
GAME	I-EVENT
DAY	I-EVENT
!	O
!	O
!	O
See	O
you	O
at	O
7	B-ORG
Card	I-ORG
Nation	I-ORG
.	O
#	O
BeACardinal	O

Cherry	B-FAC
Street	I-FAC
bus	O
stop	O
moves	O
back	O
to	O
permanent	O
location	O
October	O
23	O

For	O
the	O
strong	O
arm	O
world	O
Trump	B-PERSON
is	O
a	O
prize	O
plum	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
us	O
a	O
..............	O
g	O
disaster	O
☕	O
️	O
🚀	O

Great	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
team	O
make	O
the	O
final	O
again	O
and	O
🏴	O
󠁧󠁢󠁳󠁣󠁴󠁿	O
🏴	O
󠁧󠁢󠁷󠁬󠁳󠁿	O
and	O
🏴	O
󠁧󠁢󠁥󠁮󠁧󠁿	O
all	O
represented	O
on	O
the	O
scoresheet	O
today	O

Finally	O
got	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
and	O
ate	O
it	O
in	O
two	O
escalator	O
rides	O
,	O
so	O
make	O
of	O
that	O
what	O
you	O
will	O
.	O

Them	O
clowns	O
begged	O
so	O
hard	O
the	O
developer	O
literally	O
had	O
to	O
put	O
they	O
clown	O
asses	O
in	O
check	O
!	O
😂	O

Note	O
the	O
eyeshadow	O
matches	O
my	O
crushed	O
satin	O
top	O
?	O
And	O
my	O
earrings	O
match	O
my	O
braces	O
?	O
That	O
bow	O
tie	O
is	O
alllll	O
leather	O
too	O

It	O
's	O
so	O
close	O
yet	O
so	O
far	O
till	O
the	O
real	O
game	O
comes	O
out	O
....	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
go	O
though	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
good	O
for	O
you	O
.	O

Separating	O
fact	O
from	O
fiction	O
while	O
we	O
deal	O
with	O
the	O
5	O
stages	O
of	O
grief	O
.	O

Now	O
playing	O
disco	O
pop	O
rock	O
music	O
np	O
My	B-WORK_OF_ART
Favourite	I-WORK_OF_ART
Game	I-WORK_OF_ART
by	O
The	B-WORK_OF_ART
Cardigans	I-WORK_OF_ART
on	O
Buy	O
song	O

Will	O
I	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
load	O
my	O
xbox	B-PRODUCT
save	O
game	O
to	O
the	O
pc	O
?	O

Grass	O
fire	O
with	O
smoke	O
so	O
thick	O
it	O
blocked	O
out	O
the	O
sun	O
and	O
closed	O
Johnston	B-FAC
Road	I-FAC
in	O
West	B-FAC
Fort	I-FAC
Pierce	I-FAC
yesterday	O
...	O

I	O
hope	O
whoever	O
car	O
flipped	O
by	O
the	O
call	O
center	O
ok	O
🥴	O
🥴	O
shit	O
looked	O
a	O
scary	O

