#0
#JUST GIVE ME BACK MY ALPHABET SCROLL BAR, @ SPOTIFY
JUST	O
GIVE	O
ME	O
BACK	O
MY	O
ALPHABET	O
SCROLL	O
BAR	O
,	O
@	O
SPOTIFY	B-ORG

#1
#@edwin_thoen She's clearly been teaching the 5yo more than just the alphabet.
@edwin_thoen	O
She	O
's	O
clearly	O
been	O
teaching	O
the	O
5yo	B-ORDINAL
more	O
than	O
just	O
the	O
alphabet	O
.	O

#2
#Buich Encore🏡✅✅😎😎😎 easy to park . Commented by Lance Nov 28, 10:14 PM https://t.co/NQA8Vd0rv8 https://t.co/XJpK8mXQgO
Buich	B-PERSON
Encore	I-PERSON
🏡	O
✅	B-CARDINAL
✅	O
😎	O
😎	O
😎	O
easy	O
to	O
park	O
.	O
Commented	O
by	O
Lance	B-ORG
Nov	I-ORG
28	I-ORG
,	O
10:14	B-TIME
PM	I-TIME
https://t.co/NQA8Vd0rv8	O
https://t.co/XJpK8mXQgO	O

#3
#Apple AirPods with Charging Case, 2nd Generation ONLY $129.00 Shipped - https://t.co/sqHWEfpWtE https://t.co/Z7JMNIL1Cn
Apple	O
AirPods	O
with	O
Charging	O
Case	O
,	O
2nd	O
Generation	O
ONLY	O
$	O
129.00	O
Shipped	O
-	O
https://t.co/sqHWEfpWtE	O
https://t.co/Z7JMNIL1Cn	O

#4
##iPhone11ProMax buyer finds USB-A cable in retail box 🤔 Full story 👉 https://t.co/b6m0zPWPjR #apple #iphone 😖 https://t.co/4imu3zGxMl
\#	B-CARDINAL
iPhone11ProMax	O
buyer	O
finds	O
USB-A	O
cable	O
in	O
retail	O
box	O
🤔	O
Full	O
story	O
👉	O
https://t.co/b6m0zPWPjR	O
\#	O
apple	O
\#	O
iphone	B-GPE
😖	O
https://t.co/4imu3zGxMl	O

#5
#A scarred face, a wounded heart. REMEMBER TO FORGET https://t.co/tlOzV4HAJv #faith #militaryromance #romancenovels
A	O
scarred	O
face	O
,	O
a	O
wounded	O
heart	O
.	O
REMEMBER	O
TO	O
FORGET	O
https://t.co/tlOzV4HAJv	O
\#	O
faith	O
\#	O
militaryromance	O
\#	O
romancenovels	O

#6
#Want to be highly effective? Take it from here: https://t.co/2I48u0qipp
Want	O
to	O
be	O
highly	O
effective	O
?	O
Take	O
it	O
from	O
here	O
:	O
https://t.co/2I48u0qipp	O

#7
#Manage #ebay #amazon #pinterest products and sales #business all from one place! https://t.co/Jpr9PDvFkN
Manage	O
\#	B-MONEY
ebay	I-MONEY
\#	I-MONEY
amazon	O
\#	O
pinterest	O
products	O
and	O
sales	O
\#	B-CARDINAL
business	O
all	O
from	O
one	B-CARDINAL
place	O
!	O
https://t.co/Jpr9PDvFkN	O

#8
#6 key things Arsenal's new manager must resolve at the Emirates https://t.co/q3OC5m7TVJ https://t.co/xGFojUrwIa
6	B-CARDINAL
key	O
things	O
Arsenal	B-PRODUCT
's	O
new	O
manager	O
must	O
resolve	O
at	O
the	O
Emirates	B-GPE
https://t.co/q3OC5m7TVJ	O
https://t.co/xGFojUrwIa	O

#9
#@TheRealPro7 We hope you enjoy your rides everywhere 🖤[2/2]
@TheRealPro7	O
We	O
hope	O
you	O
enjoy	O
your	O
rides	O
everywhere	O
🖤	O
[	O
2/2	O
]	O

#10
#Schrodinger’s Cab Firm: Uber’s Existential Crisis https://t.co/5nPPn3LL4H
Schrodinger	B-ORG
’s	I-ORG
Cab	I-ORG
Firm	I-ORG
:	I-ORG
Uber	B-ORG
’s	I-ORG
Existential	I-ORG
Crisis	I-ORG
https://t.co/5nPPn3LL4H	I-ORG

#11
#It’s sooo annoying just take Uber everywhere https://t.co/TtUFODKXtc
It	O
’s	O
sooo	O
annoying	O
just	O
take	O
Uber	O
everywhere	O
https://t.co/TtUFODKXtc	O

#12
#@FutbolBible If you foul Dembele on FIFA 19/20, he gets injured in real life.. He's not been lucky @ all with injuries.
@FutbolBible	O
If	O
you	O
foul	O
Dembele	B-PERSON
on	O
FIFA	B-DATE
19/20	I-DATE
,	O
he	O
gets	O
injured	O
in	O
real	O
life	O
..	O
He	O
's	O
not	O
been	O
lucky	O
@	O
all	O
with	O
injuries	O
.	O

#13
#@Castro1021 Fifa points are always appreciated good sir
@Castro1021	O
Fifa	B-ORG
points	O
are	O
always	O
appreciated	O
good	O
sir	O

#14
#Lion Links: Higuita weighs in on his future, Orlando City thankful, FIFA rankings, and more! https://t.co/heJtUc8DRR
Lion	O
Links	O
:	O
Higuita	B-PERSON
weighs	O
in	O
on	O
his	O
future	O
,	O
Orlando	B-GPE
City	I-GPE
thankful	O
,	O
FIFA	B-ORG
rankings	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
!	O
https://t.co/heJtUc8DRR	O

#15
#Enjoy my rewards today! FIFA 20 ROAD TO GLORY #80 - MY BEST RED PICK?! https://t.co/FlbNKndDaU https://t.co/BynZwGOqLE
Enjoy	O
my	O
rewards	O
today	B-DATE
!	O
FIFA	O
20	O
ROAD	O
TO	O
GLORY	O
\#	O
80	B-MONEY
-	O
MY	O
BEST	O
RED	O
PICK	O
?	O
!	O
https://t.co/FlbNKndDaU	O
https://t.co/BynZwGOqLE	O

#16
#3. Lost A life if there's korean alphabet on your bio
3	B-CARDINAL
.	O
Lost	O
A	O
life	O
if	O
there	O
's	O
korean	B-NORP
alphabet	O
on	O
your	O
bio	O

#17
#Foreign Language Blocks | Spanish, Mandarin, Chinese, Alphabet, ABC, Bilingual Baby https://t.co/FMiQpjQaDr
Foreign	O
Language	O
Blocks	O
|	O
Spanish	B-NORP
,	O
Mandarin	B-LANGUAGE
,	O
Chinese	B-NORP
,	O
Alphabet	B-ORG
,	O
ABC	B-ORG
,	O
Bilingual	B-ORG
Baby	I-ORG
https://t.co/FMiQpjQaDr	I-ORG

#18
#@garius Which makes even less sense because they use a different alphabet. Again, flyboys.
@garius	O
Which	O
makes	O
even	O
less	O
sense	O
because	O
they	O
use	O
a	O
different	O
alphabet	O
.	O
Again	O
,	O
flyboys	O
.	O

#19
#@bangtaellectual Š is a legit letter in croatian alphabet and its so funny to me cuz it sounds like “jesush” in my head 😂😭😭
@bangtaellectual	O
Š	O
is	O
a	O
legit	O
letter	O
in	O
croatian	B-NORP
alphabet	O
and	O
its	O
so	O
funny	O
to	O
me	O
cuz	O
it	O
sounds	O
like	O
“	O
jesush	B-PERSON
”	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
😂	O
😭	O
😭	O

#20
#Check out Royal vector alphabet by Guten Tag Vector at Creative Market https://t.co/hiirz4t
Check	O
out	O
Royal	O
vector	O
alphabet	O
by	O
Guten	B-ORG
Tag	I-ORG
Vector	I-ORG
at	O
Creative	O
Market	O
https://t.co/hiirz4t	O

#21
#Google Cloud’s Bare Metal Solution Aims at Legacy Workloads with Baggage https://t.co/jpyBPwMipi https://t.co/vh1ZReyCmb
Google	B-ORG
Cloud	I-ORG
’s	I-ORG
Bare	I-ORG
Metal	I-ORG
Solution	I-ORG
Aims	I-ORG
at	O
Legacy	B-WORK_OF_ART
Workloads	I-WORK_OF_ART
with	I-WORK_OF_ART
Baggage	I-WORK_OF_ART
https://t.co/jpyBPwMipi	O
https://t.co/vh1ZReyCmb	O

#22
#@bechillcomedian I’d never have learned the first 3 letters of the alphabet if it weren’t for the Jacksons..
@bechillcomedian	B-NORP
I	O
’d	O
never	O
have	O
learned	O
the	O
first	B-ORDINAL
3	B-CARDINAL
letters	O
of	O
the	O
alphabet	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
n’t	O
for	O
the	O
Jacksons	B-PERSON
..	O

#23
#JUST GIVE ME BACK MY ALPHABET SCROLL BAR, @ SPOTIFY
JUST	O
GIVE	O
ME	O
BACK	O
MY	O
ALPHABET	O
SCROLL	O
BAR	O
,	O
@	O
SPOTIFY	B-ORG

#24
#@edwin_thoen She's clearly been teaching the 5yo more than just the alphabet.
@edwin_thoen	O
She	O
's	O
clearly	O
been	O
teaching	O
the	O
5yo	B-ORDINAL
more	O
than	O
just	O
the	O
alphabet	O
.	O

#25
#@imshin @leekern13 @jeremycorbyn I also enjoyed Prince Whatshisname's visit but was a bit upset that he didn't sing Alphabet Street.
@imshin	O
@leekern13	O
@jeremycorbyn	O
I	O
also	O
enjoyed	O
Prince	B-PERSON
Whatshisname	I-PERSON
's	I-PERSON
visit	O
but	O
was	O
a	O
bit	O
upset	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
n't	O
sing	O
Alphabet	B-FAC
Street	I-FAC
.	O

#26
#@wahcry i feel like he doing the alphabet with an accent
@wahcry	B-ORG
i	O
feel	O
like	O
he	O
doing	O
the	O
alphabet	O
with	O
an	O
accent	O

#27
#Poems sizzle in her fingertips .. paper aches for the flow of passion in the form of an unknown alphabet....
Poems	O
sizzle	O
in	O
her	O
fingertips	O
..	O
paper	O
aches	O
for	O
the	O
flow	O
of	O
passion	O
in	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
an	O
unknown	O
alphabet	O
....	O

#28
#@SRKUniverse no speak hindi with english alphabet no don't
@SRKUniverse	O
no	O
speak	O
hindi	O
with	O
english	B-LANGUAGE
alphabet	O
no	O
do	O
n't	O

#29
#@KaieSayh Their first letters follow each other in the alphabet too.😂
@KaieSayh	O
Their	O
first	B-ORDINAL
letters	O
follow	O
each	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
alphabet	O
too	O
.	O
😂	O

#30
#If Plan A didn't work, its ok because alphabet has 25 more letters... Stay Cool !
If	O
Plan	O
A	O
did	O
n't	O
work	O
,	O
its	O
ok	O
because	O
alphabet	O
has	O
25	B-CARDINAL
more	O
letters	O
...	O
Stay	O
Cool	O
!	O

#31
#memorize this alphabet rap cause of this video lmAo https://t.co/II1sknTeRR
memorize	O
this	O
alphabet	O
rap	O
cause	O
of	O
this	O
video	O
lmAo	O
https://t.co/II1sknTeRR	O

#32
#Alphabet Games (Atlantis Software, year unknown) https://t.co/y0tY4JwE1r https://t.co/2iz5z3xI7V
Alphabet	O
Games	O
(	O
Atlantis	O
Software	O
,	O
year	O
unknown	O
)	O
https://t.co/y0tY4JwE1r	O
https://t.co/2iz5z3xI7V	O

#33
#@GeraldKutney @fordnation @AndrewScheer @jkenney The New Science: "forget letters of the alphabet, such as E" https://t.co/skXGRc5iHV
@GeraldKutney	O
@fordnation	O
@AndrewScheer	O
@jkenney	O
The	O
New	O
Science	O
:	O
"	O
forget	O
letters	O
of	O
the	O
alphabet	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
E	O
"	O
https://t.co/skXGRc5iHV	O

#34
#If I could rearrange the alphabet I would put U and I together. 11:57 #arseclock
If	O
I	O
could	O
rearrange	O
the	O
alphabet	O
I	O
would	O
put	O
U	O
and	O
I	O
together	O
.	O
11:57	O
\#	O
arseclock	O

#35
#in another lifetime the alphabet will be blessed with rain
in	O
another	O
lifetime	O
the	O
alphabet	O
will	O
be	O
blessed	O
with	O
rain	O

#36
#@B_hundred_Hyun bro 백현 why didntyou see alphabet mentions too ╥﹏╥
@B_hundred_Hyun	O
bro	O
백현	O
why	O
didntyou	O
see	O
alphabet	O
mentions	O
too	O
╥	B-ORG
﹏	O
╥	B-ORG

#37
#Kids Fun Learning Alphabet Small Letters Education in Bangla-part-8 https://t.co/6BEhg8mnQd via @YouTube
Kids	O
Fun	O
Learning	O
Alphabet	O
Small	O
Letters	O
Education	O
in	O
Bangla-part-8	O
https://t.co/6BEhg8mnQd	O
via	O
@YouTube	O

#38
#@alexhern What is your signature dish? Because I always think of signing things and alphabet spaghetti
@alexhern	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
signature	O
dish	O
?	O
Because	O
I	O
always	O
think	O
of	O
signing	O
things	O
and	O
alphabet	O
spaghetti	O

#39
#@elonmusk buy and delete Indian media please #BuyAndDeleteIndianMedia
@elonmusk	B-ORG
buy	O
and	O
delete	O
Indian	B-NORP
media	O
please	O
\#	B-MONEY
BuyAndDeleteIndianMedia	I-MONEY

#40
#Loveable television celebrity drops his guard. The apple didn’t fall far from this tree! https://t.co/LBJgxkILUa
Loveable	O
television	O
celebrity	O
drops	O
his	O
guard	O
.	O
The	O
apple	O
did	O
n’t	O
fall	O
far	O
from	O
this	O
tree	O
!	O
https://t.co/LBJgxkILUa	O

#41
#The Apple never falls far from the tree. https://t.co/IpyiphefjQ
The	O
Apple	B-ORG
never	O
falls	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
tree	O
.	O
https://t.co/IpyiphefjQ	O

#42
#If you are looking for niche, targeted content for your publication, try Owen Jones on Kobo, Kindle, BandN, Apple, etc https://t.co/gbda0AHL7G
If	O
you	O
are	O
looking	O
for	O
niche	O
,	O
targeted	O
content	O
for	O
your	O
publication	O
,	O
try	O
Owen	B-PERSON
Jones	I-PERSON
on	O
Kobo	B-ORG
,	O
Kindle	B-PRODUCT
,	O
BandN	O
,	O
Apple	B-ORG
,	O
etc	O
https://t.co/gbda0AHL7G	O

#43
#Attempt #522 @theneedledrop give my new EP a listen and tell me what you think?? 🙏 https://t.co/CuCyB28IDU
Attempt	O
\#	O
522	B-MONEY
@theneedledrop	B-ORG
give	O
my	O
new	O
EP	O
a	O
listen	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
you	O
think	O
?	O
?	O
🙏	O
https://t.co/CuCyB28IDU	O

#44
#@Cum_To_Me_XxX Thanks for following us! The app is now live on iOS at https://t.co/KNI1ZIca59 and Android at https://t.co/Q9bQlBtXKx!
@Cum_To_Me_XxX	O
Thanks	O
for	O
following	O
us	O
!	O
The	O
app	O
is	O
now	O
live	O
on	O
iOS	O
at	O
https://t.co/KNI1ZIca59	O
and	O
Android	O
at	O
https://t.co/Q9bQlBtXKx	O
!	O

#45
#im sorry apple fans but apple devices are really, really bad
i	O
m	O
sorry	O
apple	O
fans	O
but	O
apple	O
devices	O
are	O
really	O
,	O
really	O
bad	O

#46
#Apple Black Friday deal: HomePod down to $199.99 at Best Buy https://t.co/LjRBtibqwq https://t.co/BmV4LwMRce
Apple	B-ORG
Black	I-ORG
Friday	B-DATE
deal	O
:	O
HomePod	B-PERSON
down	O
to	O
$	O
199.99	B-MONEY
at	O
Best	O
Buy	O
https://t.co/LjRBtibqwq	O
https://t.co/BmV4LwMRce	O

#47
#@LewisSports @ToveTupper @DanLewisNews Happy Thanksgiving, Apple Cup and Black Friday Lewis's ... enjoy! #lewis
@LewisSports	O
@ToveTupper	O
@DanLewisNews	O
Happy	O
Thanksgiving	B-DATE
,	O
Apple	B-ORG
Cup	I-ORG
and	O
Black	O
Friday	B-DATE
Lewis	B-PERSON
's	O
...	O
enjoy	O
!	O
\#	O
lewis	B-PERSON

#48
#26. i don't sleep with music on so another song from my 3am playlist https://t.co/lEszy5r0xF
26	B-CARDINAL
.	O
i	O
do	O
n't	O
sleep	O
with	O
music	O
on	O
so	O
another	O
song	O
from	O
my	O
3	B-CARDINAL
am	O
playlist	O
https://t.co/lEszy5r0xF	O

#49
#25. i could cheat and put kpop or russian song but! i have a song in latvian :> https://t.co/n4F8JT9BCT
25	B-CARDINAL
.	O
i	O
could	O
cheat	O
and	O
put	O
kpop	O
or	O
russian	B-NORP
song	O
but	O
!	O
i	O
have	O
a	O
song	O
in	O
latvian	B-NORP
:>	O
https://t.co/n4F8JT9BCT	O

#50
#24. hhh i always have a song stuck in my head .. rn https://t.co/AflMf0LVEt
24	B-CARDINAL
.	O
hhh	B-PERSON
i	O
always	O
have	O
a	O
song	O
stuck	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
..	O
rn	B-PERSON
https://t.co/AflMf0LVEt	O

#51
#Au revoir Apple you crook — Jony Ive has left Apple https://t.co/uFiPPBso6G
Au	O
revoir	O
Apple	O
you	O
crook	O
—	O
Jony	B-PERSON
I	O
ve	O
has	O
left	O
Apple	B-ORG
https://t.co/uFiPPBso6G	O

#52
#22. yeah time for my fall out boy obsession to shine https://t.co/ouihUoXKys
22	B-CARDINAL
.	O
yeah	O
time	O
for	O
my	O
fall	O
out	O
boy	O
obsession	O
to	O
shine	O
https://t.co/ouihUoXKys	O

#53
#21. oh i have a whole playlist of these bad boys too... https://t.co/kqMJ1SXnIN
21	B-CARDINAL
.	O
oh	O
i	O
have	O
a	O
whole	O
playlist	O
of	O
these	O
bad	O
boys	O
too	O
...	O
https://t.co/kqMJ1SXnIN	O

#54
#@Cornish_Damo Clearly the rotten apple does not fall too far from the tree.
@Cornish_Damo	O
Clearly	O
the	O
rotten	O
apple	O
does	O
not	O
fall	O
too	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
tree	O
.	O

#55
##NOWPLAYING I Can't Help It by Canton Jones @thecantonjones Listen live via https://t.co/9zV1AAzHit Buy song https://t.co/yWxmNfDgYr
\#	O
NOWPLAYING	O
I	O
Ca	O
n't	O
Help	O
It	O
by	O
Canton	B-ORG
Jones	I-ORG
@thecantonjones	O
Listen	O
live	O
via	O
https://t.co/9zV1AAzHit	O
Buy	O
song	O
https://t.co/yWxmNfDgYr	O

#56
#I really wish ALL of @TeC_dA_CtB songs was on Apple Music 😩😩 .
I	O
really	O
wish	O
ALL	O
of	O
@TeC_dA_CtB	B-ORG
songs	O
was	O
on	O
Apple	B-ORG
Music	I-ORG
😩	I-ORG
😩	I-ORG
.	O

#57
#@TheRickWilson YASSSS!! JUST had apple crumble pie and coffee!! #ENERGIZED
@TheRickWilson	B-PERSON
YASSSS	I-PERSON
!	O
!	O
JUST	O
had	O
apple	O
crumble	O
pie	O
and	O
coffee	O
!	O
!	O
\#	B-CARDINAL
ENERGIZED	O

#58
#Get #Apple AirPods and AirPods Pro for the best prices of the year on Black Friday https://t.co/7EISqjrQjf
Get	O
\#	O
Apple	O
AirPods	O
and	O
AirPods	B-ORG
Pro	O
for	O
the	O
best	O
prices	O
of	O
the	B-DATE
year	I-DATE
on	O
Black	B-EVENT
Friday	I-EVENT
https://t.co/7EISqjrQjf	O

#59
#How to unpair an #Apple Watch https://t.co/GvHk79k3OG
How	O
to	O
unpair	B-ORG
an	O
\#	B-CARDINAL
Apple	B-ORG
Watch	I-ORG
https://t.co/GvHk79k3OG	O

#60
#@AAJ_Pragamatist Actually it doesn’t have the date - it just says Willem’s Apple. I’ll get him to add the date - thanks!
@AAJ_Pragamatist	O
Actually	O
it	O
does	O
n’t	O
have	O
the	O
date	O
-	O
it	O
just	O
says	O
Willem	B-PERSON
’s	I-PERSON
Apple	I-PERSON
.	O
I	O
’ll	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
add	O
the	O
date	O
-	O
thanks	O
!	O

#61
#Apple’s Black Friday sale is live, and it stinks – here are all the best Apple deals https://t.co/360SNtPerl
Apple	B-ORG
’s	O
Black	O
Friday	B-DATE
sale	O
is	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
stinks	O
–	O
here	O
are	O
all	O
the	O
best	O
Apple	B-ORG
deals	O
https://t.co/360SNtPerl	O

#62
##NowPlaying What Have You Done by KWAYE on https://t.co/NaQUi8RgZO https://t.co/JglWTGD8BK
\#	O
NowPlaying	B-ORG
What	O
Have	O
You	O
Done	O
by	O
KWAYE	B-PERSON
on	O
https://t.co/NaQUi8RgZO	O
https://t.co/JglWTGD8BK	O

#63
#Horrible act legitimized by Apple! WTF?!😠 https://t.co/tpQ5loo4II
Horrible	O
act	O
legitimized	O
by	O
Apple	B-ORG
!	O
WTF	B-PERSON
?	O
!	O
😠	O
https://t.co/tpQ5loo4II	O

#64
#The Apple iPhone XR is on sale for #blackfriday . https://t.co/HlaTVzqaEN
The	O
Apple	B-ORG
iPhone	O
XR	B-ORG
is	O
on	O
sale	O
for	O
\#	O
blackfriday	B-DATE
.	O
https://t.co/HlaTVzqaEN	O

#65
#Check out this Amazon deal: Fire HD 8 Tablet (8' HD Display, 16 GB) - Black by Amazon https://t.co/lfX8khbTDC via @amazon
Check	O
out	O
this	O
Amazon	B-ORG
deal	O
:	O
Fire	O
HD	O
8	B-CARDINAL
Tablet	O
(	O
8	B-CARDINAL
'	O
HD	O
Display	O
,	O
16	B-CARDINAL
GB	O
)	O
-	O
Black	O
by	O
Amazon	B-PERSON
https://t.co/lfX8khbTDC	I-PERSON
via	O
@amazon	B-ORG

#66
#Help us out! Use this link when you go to shop Amazon this Christmas season! https://t.co/uXl7uopRIP https://t.co/Xv2fELqgXU
Help	O
us	O
out	O
!	O
Use	O
this	O
link	O
when	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
shop	O
Amazon	B-ORG
this	B-DATE
Christmas	I-DATE
season	I-DATE
!	O
https://t.co/uXl7uopRIP	O
https://t.co/Xv2fELqgXU	O

#67
#CASTELBAJAC Weight Shoulder bag 090911 khaki JCC https://t.co/fNSxTaCf89 via amazon
CASTELBAJAC	B-ORG
Weight	O
Shoulder	O
bag	O
090911	B-DATE
khaki	B-ORG
JCC	I-ORG
https://t.co/fNSxTaCf89	O
via	O
amazon	B-ORG

#68
#$AMZN $UPS $FDX $AAWW: Amazon, UPS, FedEx cargo pilots seek more rest as busy holiday shipping season begins: https://t.co/u8lASRFUgn
$	O
AMZN	O
$	O
UPS	O
$	O
FDX	O
$	O
AAWW	B-ORG
:	O
Amazon	B-ORG
,	O
UPS	B-ORG
,	O
FedEx	B-ORG
cargo	O
pilots	O
seek	O
more	O
rest	O
as	O
busy	O
holiday	O
shipping	O
season	O
begins	O
:	O
https://t.co/u8lASRFUgn	O

#69
#@savethecat Sadly, not from Amazon UK 😢 https://t.co/xN7viU2HRn
@savethecat	O
Sadly	O
,	O
not	O
from	O
Amazon	B-ORG
UK	I-ORG
😢	O
https://t.co/xN7viU2HRn	O

#70
#£40 Amazon gift card? Thank you TalkTalk for this Black Friday broadband deal https://t.co/PIdmv8826y https://t.co/QQS345jLdv
£	O
40	B-MONEY
Amazon	B-ORG
gift	O
card	O
?	O
Thank	O
you	O
TalkTalk	B-ORG
for	O
this	O
Black	O
Friday	B-DATE
broadband	O
deal	O
https://t.co/PIdmv8826y	B-CARDINAL
https://t.co/QQS345jLdv	O

#71
#Roblox Gift Card - 800 Robux [Online Game Code] #Roblox #Gift #Card https://t.co/7ap4FLK639
Roblox	B-ORG
Gift	O
Card	O
-	O
800	O
Robux	O
[	O
Online	O
Game	B-LAW
Code	I-LAW
]	O
\#	B-MONEY
Roblox	I-MONEY
\#	I-MONEY
Gift	O
\#	O
Card	O
https://t.co/7ap4FLK639	O

#72
#BBC News - Black Friday protest: French activists block Amazon warehouse https://t.co/0KkQhtXqdQ
BBC	B-ORG
News	I-ORG
-	I-ORG
Black	I-ORG
Friday	B-DATE
protest	O
:	O
French	B-NORP
activists	O
block	O
Amazon	B-ORG
warehouse	O
https://t.co/0KkQhtXqdQ	O

#73
#@MSNBC Wow, no thanks @amazon I'd rather wait an extra day for my Chinese made junk than have someone shitting next to my package...
@MSNBC	O
Wow	O
,	O
no	O
thanks	O
@amazon	B-PERSON
I	O
'd	O
rather	O
wait	O
an	B-DATE
extra	I-DATE
day	I-DATE
for	O
my	O
Chinese	B-NORP
made	O
junk	O
than	O
have	O
someone	O
shitting	O
next	O
to	O
my	O
package	O
...	O

#74
#Live gold de R$149 por R$129 https://t.co/hbqJzclo3w via @amazon
Live	O
gold	O
de	O
R$149	O
por	O
R$129	O
https://t.co/hbqJzclo3w	O
via	O
@amazon	O

#75
#@AnupamPKher @AdityaRajKaul @HotelMumbaiFilm Already watched in amazon prime video
@AnupamPKher	B-ORG
@AdityaRajKaul	I-ORG
@HotelMumbaiFilm	O
Already	O
watched	O
in	O
amazon	B-ORG
prime	O
video	O

#76
#The best Amazon deals in the Black Friday 2019 sale https://t.co/8JKiUWttkv
The	O
best	O
Amazon	B-ORG
deals	O
in	O
the	O
Black	B-EVENT
Friday	I-EVENT
2019	B-DATE
sale	O
https://t.co/8JKiUWttkv	O

#77
##HuaweiWatchGT2 will be sold through #Amazon and #Flipkart in #India https://t.co/MTDaRIqBwe
\#	B-CARDINAL
HuaweiWatchGT2	O
will	O
be	O
sold	O
through	O
\#	O
Amazon	B-ORG
and	O
\#	B-CARDINAL
Flipkart	B-ORG
in	O
\#	O
India	B-GPE
https://t.co/MTDaRIqBwe	O

#78
#@wirecutter Yep it’s great. Even if the interface is kinda bad. Also for some reason it doesn’t have amazon prime video in Canada.
@wirecutter	O
Yep	O
it	O
’s	O
great	O
.	O
Even	O
if	O
the	O
interface	O
is	O
kinda	O
bad	O
.	O
Also	O
for	O
some	O
reason	O
it	O
does	O
n’t	O
have	O
amazon	B-ORG
prime	O
video	O
in	O
Canada	B-GPE
.	O

#79
#Enjoy with good rock disco pop music np 4:00 AM by Tahiti 80 on https://t.co/GsPb9Nfjqi Buy song https://t.co/jTXChV3U4T
Enjoy	O
with	O
good	O
rock	O
disco	O
pop	O
music	O
np	B-ORG
4:00	B-TIME
AM	I-TIME
by	O
Tahiti	B-GPE
80	I-GPE
on	O
https://t.co/GsPb9Nfjqi	O
Buy	O
song	O
https://t.co/jTXChV3U4T	O

#80
##NowPlaying Live365 - ADBREAK_60000 3 :: Tune In : https://t.co/PA3x4XaDq9 - Buy It https://t.co/altwBfY2cS https://t.co/89cpRJKPr9
\#	O
NowPlaying	O
Live365	O
-	O
ADBREAK_60000	O
3	B-CARDINAL
:	O
:	O
Tune	O
In	O
:	O
https://t.co/PA3x4XaDq9	O
-	O
Buy	O
It	O
https://t.co/altwBfY2cS	O
https://t.co/89cpRJKPr9	O

#81
##NowPlaying Bout Me by EarlyTime @258Mafia https://t.co/8lluUgZIzj Buy song https://t.co/JKxuEH44Tb https://t.co/32bWqKGt5J
\#	O
NowPlaying	B-PERSON
Bout	O
Me	O
by	O
EarlyTime	B-ORG
@258Mafia	O
https://t.co/8lluUgZIzj	O
Buy	O
song	O
https://t.co/JKxuEH44Tb	O
https://t.co/32bWqKGt5J	O

#82
#Black Friday protest: French activists block Amazon warehouse https://t.co/ihGotKSw6a https://t.co/DLsp8bfqOn
Black	O
Friday	B-DATE
protest	O
:	O
French	B-NORP
activists	O
block	O
Amazon	B-ORG
warehouse	O
https://t.co/ihGotKSw6a	O
https://t.co/DLsp8bfqOn	O

#83
#Get #Apple AirPods and AirPods Pro for the best prices of the year on Black Friday https://t.co/7EISqjrQjf
Get	O
\#	O
Apple	O
AirPods	O
and	O
AirPods	B-ORG
Pro	O
for	O
the	O
best	O
prices	O
of	O
the	B-DATE
year	I-DATE
on	O
Black	B-EVENT
Friday	I-EVENT
https://t.co/7EISqjrQjf	O

#84
#BLACK FRIDAY : L'ARNAQUE AMAZON https://t.co/lcc89QGiuM via @YouTube
BLACK	O
FRIDAY	B-DATE
:	O
L'ARNAQUE	O
AMAZON	B-ORG
https://t.co/lcc89QGiuM	O
via	O
@YouTube	O

#85
#via @instapundit: AT AMAZON, shop Black Friday deals today. https://t.co/FAkMZi67lc
via	O
@instapundit	O
:	O
AT	O
AMAZON	B-ORG
,	O
shop	O
Black	B-EVENT
Friday	I-EVENT
deals	O
today	B-DATE
.	O
https://t.co/FAkMZi67lc	O

#86
#His mother was killed by a van making Amazon deliveries — here’s the letter he wrote to Jeff Bezos https://t.co/cnhQBymfgN
His	O
mother	O
was	O
killed	O
by	O
a	O
van	O
making	O
Amazon	B-ORG
deliveries	O
—	O
here	O
’s	O
the	O
letter	O
he	O
wrote	O
to	O
Jeff	B-PERSON
Bezos	I-PERSON
https://t.co/cnhQBymfgN	O

#87
#@no1stuntmaster @SenseiSw1tch Amazon and curry's. Price matching.
@no1stuntmaster	O
@SenseiSw1tch	O
Amazon	O
and	O
curry	O
's	O
.	O
Price	O
matching	O
.	O

#88
#@SilverStorm100 I’m scouting amazon for Pokémon hats lol and possibly whatever else catches my eye lol
@SilverStorm100	O
I	O
’m	O
scouting	O
amazon	B-ORG
for	O
Pokémon	B-ORG
hats	O
lol	O
and	O
possibly	O
whatever	O
else	O
catches	O
my	O
eye	O
lol	O

#89
#I could give up #shopping but I'm not a quitter. Let's go shopping https://t.co/zZb9aO30tq https://t.co/aUCPr4CDNv
I	O
could	O
give	O
up	O
\#	B-CARDINAL
shopping	O
but	O
I	O
'm	O
not	O
a	O
quitter	O
.	O
Let	O
's	O
go	O
shopping	O
https://t.co/zZb9aO30tq	O
https://t.co/aUCPr4CDNv	B-CARDINAL

#90
#My furniture payment went through I'm so fucking broke amazon ple give me my refund https://t.co/z7DjZ6ODtV
My	O
furniture	O
payment	O
went	O
through	O
I	O
'm	O
so	O
fucking	O
broke	O
amazon	B-PERSON
ple	I-PERSON
give	O
me	O
my	O
refund	O
https://t.co/z7DjZ6ODtV	O

#91
#There's enough residual disclosure in this article for Amazon to identify this woman. https://t.co/LPvB3vAi9m
There	O
's	O
enough	O
residual	O
disclosure	O
in	O
this	O
article	O
for	O
Amazon	B-ORG
to	O
identify	O
this	O
woman	O
.	O
https://t.co/LPvB3vAi9m	O

#92
##Symphysodon, colloquially known as #discus, is a genus of #cichlids native to the Amazon river basin.
\#	O
Symphysodon	B-PERSON
,	O
colloquially	O
known	O
as	O
\#	O
discus	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
genus	O
of	O
\#	B-CARDINAL
cichlids	O
native	O
to	O
the	O
Amazon	B-LOC
river	I-LOC
basin	O
.	O

#93
#I haven’t had McDonalds in 4 weeks now. I’m going blind in one eye.
I	O
have	O
n’t	O
had	O
McDonalds	B-ORG
in	O
4	B-DATE
weeks	I-DATE
now	O
.	O
I	O
’m	O
going	O
blind	O
in	O
one	B-CARDINAL
eye	O
.	O

#94
#@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Lies! He would rather be eating McDonalds in bed.
@WhiteHouse	O
@realDonaldTrump	O
Lies	O
!	O
He	O
would	O
rather	O
be	O
eating	O
McDonalds	B-ORG
in	O
bed	O
.	O

#95
#Nobody: Vegans: “McDonald’s needs to come to an end!” @McDonalds : “McFuckincuse me!!!???”
Nobody	O
:	O
Vegans	O
:	O
“	O
McDonald	B-ORG
’s	I-ORG
needs	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
an	O
end	O
!	O
”	O
@McDonalds	O
:	O
“	O
McFuckincuse	B-PERSON
me	O
!	O
!	O
!	O
?	O
?	O
?	O
”	O

#96
#'What do you call this? Looks like Homer Simpson sat on it' https://t.co/wAnxqyzP7M
'	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
this	O
?	O
Looks	O
like	O
Homer	B-PERSON
Simpson	I-PERSON
sat	O
on	O
it	O
'	O
https://t.co/wAnxqyzP7M	O

#97
#ik mafuteru ebook's gimmick is abt being a mcdonalds stan acc but. wanna know a fun fact. i actually like burger king more
ik	O
mafuteru	B-PERSON
ebook	I-PERSON
's	I-PERSON
gimmick	O
is	O
abt	O
being	O
a	O
mcdonalds	B-ORG
stan	I-ORG
acc	I-ORG
but	O
.	O
wanna	O
know	O
a	O
fun	O
fact	O
.	O
i	O
actually	O
like	O
burger	O
king	O
more	O

#98
#Why y’all get on this mf and just lie? We hate y’all got a fat ass half a McDonalds sign?? Like cmon https://t.co/EONpyDl3k7
Why	O
y’	O
all	O
get	O
on	O
this	O
mf	O
and	O
just	O
lie	O
?	O
We	O
hate	O
y’	O
all	O
got	O
a	O
fat	O
ass	O
half	B-CARDINAL
a	O
McDonalds	B-ORG
sign	O
?	O
?	O
Like	O
cmon	O
https://t.co/EONpyDl3k7	O

#99
#me: i want to #loseWeight me: i want skinny legs me: i want a #flatStomach me: i want to be thin me: *sees #mcdonalds* me: #yolo
me	O
:	O
i	O
want	O
to	O
\#	O
loseWeight	O
me	O
:	O
i	O
want	O
skinny	O
legs	O
me	O
:	O
i	O
want	O
a	O
\#	B-MONEY
flatStomach	I-MONEY
me	O
:	O
i	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
thin	O
me	O
:	O
*	O
sees	O
\#	O
mcdonalds	B-PERSON
*	O
me	O
:	O
\#	O
yolo	O

#100
#@James_Fielden That doesn't elain the NUN 0 reg plate of the car parked outside the Emirates though does it?
@James_Fielden	O
That	O
does	O
n't	O
elain	O
the	O
NUN	O
0	O
reg	O
plate	O
of	O
the	O
car	O
parked	O
outside	O
the	O
Emirates	B-GPE
though	O
does	O
it	O
?	O

#101
#Fully believe that stewards at the emirates have to check you are a bellend before letting you in
Fully	O
believe	O
that	O
stewards	O
at	O
the	O
emirates	B-GPE
have	O
to	O
check	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
bellend	O
before	O
letting	O
you	O
in	O

#102
#With Unai Emery's time at Arsenal now up, who will replace him at the Emirates Stadium? 📲 https://t.co/5h0pCMtKHn https://t.co/BLXhf2d657
With	O
Unai	B-PERSON
Emery	I-PERSON
's	I-PERSON
time	O
at	O
Arsenal	B-PRODUCT
now	O
up	O
,	O
who	O
will	O
replace	O
him	O
at	O
the	B-FAC
Emirates	I-FAC
Stadium	I-FAC
?	O
📲	O
https://t.co/5h0pCMtKHn	O
https://t.co/BLXhf2d657	O

#103
#Unai Emery has been sacked as @Arsenal head coach so who could become the Spaniard's permanent successor at the Emirates Stadium?
Unai	B-PERSON
Emery	I-PERSON
has	O
been	O
sacked	O
as	O
@Arsenal	O
head	O
coach	O
so	O
who	O
could	O
become	O
the	O
Spaniard	B-NORP
's	O
permanent	O
successor	O
at	O
the	B-FAC
Emirates	I-FAC
Stadium	I-FAC
?	O

#104
#Klopp 2nd favourite for the Arsenal job. Has John Henry tweeted asking what are they smoking at the Emirates yet?
Klopp	B-PERSON
2nd	O
favourite	O
for	O
the	O
Arsenal	B-PRODUCT
job	O
.	O
Has	O
John	B-PERSON
Henry	I-PERSON
tweeted	O
asking	O
what	O
are	O
they	O
smoking	O
at	O
the	O
Emirates	B-GPE
yet	O
?	O

#105
#@cacaochanel @EtihadAirways Try Emirates or Qatar, much better service.
@cacaochanel	B-ORG
@EtihadAirways	I-ORG
Try	O
Emirates	B-GPE
or	O
Qatar	B-GPE
,	O
much	O
better	O
service	O
.	O

#106
#Arsenal finally part ways with Unai Emery, talk about #BlackFriday at the Emirates. #COYG
Arsenal	O
finally	O
part	O
ways	O
with	O
Unai	B-PERSON
Emery	I-PERSON
,	O
talk	O
about	O
\#	O
BlackFriday	B-DATE
at	O
the	O
Emirates	B-GPE
.	O
\#	O
COYG	B-ORG

#107
##Ozil seeing #UnaiEmery leaving the emirates for the last time 😂 #arsenal #UnaiOut https://t.co/mkpMF1SP2T
\#	O
Ozil	B-PERSON
seeing	O
\#	O
UnaiEmery	B-PERSON
leaving	O
the	O
emirates	B-GPE
for	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
😂	O
\#	B-MONEY
arsenal	I-MONEY
\#	O
UnaiOut	O
https://t.co/mkpMF1SP2T	O

#108
#@David_Ornstein Don’t worry David, you’ll have a statue outside the Emirates soon
@David_Ornstein	O
Do	O
n’t	O
worry	O
David	B-PERSON
,	O
you	O
’ll	O
have	O
a	O
statue	O
outside	O
the	O
Emirates	B-GPE
soon	O

#109
#"Emirates News Agency - Ajman Ruler attends 48th National Day celebration - WAM EN" https://t.co/m782uCiZUV #Ajman
"	O
Emirates	B-ORG
News	I-ORG
Agency	I-ORG
-	O
Ajman	O
Ruler	O
attends	O
48th	B-DATE
National	I-DATE
Day	I-DATE
celebration	B-EVENT
-	I-EVENT
WAM	I-EVENT
EN	I-EVENT
"	I-EVENT
https://t.co/m782uCiZUV	I-EVENT
\#	O
Ajman	B-GPE

#110
#Unai Emery leaving The Emirates this morning https://t.co/wJ6EYZPLXx
Unai	B-PERSON
Emery	I-PERSON
leaving	O
The	O
Emirates	B-GPE
this	B-TIME
morning	I-TIME
https://t.co/wJ6EYZPLXx	O

#111
#Haramball is coming to The Emirates. And it will be beautiful. 😍 https://t.co/sW7CSbShXa
Haramball	B-PERSON
is	O
coming	O
to	O
The	O
Emirates	B-GPE
.	O
And	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
beautiful	O
.	O
😍	O
https://t.co/sW7CSbShXa	O

#112
#haha. You need to build a statue of Kamata Daichi in front of the Emirates Stadium. https://t.co/gAkEDrU6pe
haha	O
.	O
You	O
need	O
to	O
build	O
a	O
statue	O
of	O
Kamata	B-ORG
Daichi	I-ORG
in	O
front	O
of	O
the	B-FAC
Emirates	I-FAC
Stadium	I-FAC
.	O
https://t.co/gAkEDrU6pe	O

#113
#'Wenger In' signs appearing at Emirates after Unai Emery’s sacking - https://t.co/52dnaYCqjD via @newsthump
'	O
Wenger	O
In	O
'	O
signs	O
appearing	O
at	O
Emirates	B-GPE
after	O
Unai	B-PERSON
Emery	I-PERSON
’s	I-PERSON
sacking	O
-	O
https://t.co/52dnaYCqjD	O
via	O
@newsthump	O

#114
#Frankfurt chief slams Emirates Stadium as Arsenal fans stay away https://t.co/oYg9qseElj
Frankfurt	B-GPE
chief	O
slams	O
Emirates	B-FAC
Stadium	I-FAC
as	O
Arsenal	O
fans	O
stay	O
away	O
https://t.co/oYg9qseElj	O

#115
#Ray Parlour has his say on who should take over at the Emirates 🗣 https://t.co/BcuAIXTjYB
Ray	B-PERSON
Parlour	I-PERSON
has	O
his	O
say	O
on	O
who	O
should	O
take	O
over	O
at	O
the	O
Emirates	B-GPE
🗣	O
https://t.co/BcuAIXTjYB	O

#116
#I’m sure I just see Neil Warnock ushered into the Emirates 🎣⚽️
I	O
’m	O
sure	O
I	O
just	O
see	O
Neil	B-PERSON
Warnock	I-PERSON
ushered	O
into	O
the	O
Emirates	B-NORP
🎣	O
⚽	O
️	O

#117
#@afcjacques if he comes I'll be shitting myself when we travel to the Emirates😂😩
@afcjacques	B-ORG
if	O
he	O
comes	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
shitting	O
myself	O
when	O
we	O
travel	O
to	O
the	O
Emirates	B-GPE
😂	O
😩	O

#118
#Don’t drink and drive, you drunk nincompoop! Dig up the lettuce to pay your uber driver.
Do	O
n’t	O
drink	O
and	O
drive	O
,	O
you	O
drunk	O
nincompoop	O
!	O
Dig	O
up	O
the	O
lettuce	O
to	O
pay	O
your	O
uber	O
driver	O
.	O

#119
#India considers commissions cap for Uber, Ola, unsettling industry https://t.co/ofb1eY5AD8 #India #Policy #Ridehailing
India	B-GPE
considers	O
commissions	O
cap	O
for	O
Uber	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
Ola	I-ORG
,	O
unsettling	O
industry	O
https://t.co/ofb1eY5AD8	O
\#	O
India	O
\#	O
Policy	O
\#	O
Ridehailing	O

#120
#BBC News - Manchester City Council to hold emergency Uber meeting https://t.co/50MSb92BsR
BBC	B-ORG
News	I-ORG
-	I-ORG
Manchester	I-ORG
City	I-ORG
Council	I-ORG
to	O
hold	O
emergency	O
Uber	O
meeting	O
https://t.co/50MSb92BsR	O

#121
#@Uber_Kids You have not adequately replied. Please read my message in full. I’m very disappointed in your terrible customer service.
@Uber_Kids	O
You	O
have	O
not	O
adequately	O
replied	O
.	O
Please	O
read	O
my	O
message	O
in	O
full	O
.	O
I	O
’m	O
very	O
disappointed	O
in	O
your	O
terrible	O
customer	O
service	O
.	O

#122
#I’m really not good at being away from my family 😭 I was uber sad yesterday
I	O
’m	O
really	O
not	O
good	O
at	O
being	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
family	O
😭	O
I	O
was	O
uber	O
sad	O
yesterday	B-DATE

#123
#@rubykmo @Uber I know ... they haven’t even got in contact yet......... 🙃
@rubykmo	B-PERSON
@Uber	O
I	O
know	O
...	O
they	O
have	O
n’t	O
even	O
got	O
in	O
contact	O
yet	O
.........	O
🙃	O

#124
#Idk what’s worse. Me ordering food at 5am or the Uber driver delivering food at 5am. https://t.co/cYzmqltClo
Idk	O
what	O
’s	O
worse	O
.	O
Me	O
ordering	O
food	O
at	O
5	B-CARDINAL
am	O
or	O
the	O
Uber	B-ORG
driver	O
delivering	O
food	O
at	O
5	B-CARDINAL
am	O
.	O
https://t.co/cYzmqltClo	O

#125
#deffo catching Uber while I bleed out https://t.co/qdhYYRaz5i
deffo	O
catching	O
Uber	O
while	O
I	O
bleed	O
out	O
https://t.co/qdhYYRaz5i	O

#126
#Uber Eats delivery guy arrives* Me: “So what are we?”
Uber	O
Eats	O
delivery	O
guy	O
arrives	O
*	O
Me	O
:	O
“	O
So	O
what	O
are	O
we	O
?	O
”	O

#127
#@Fxngc Network network huit uber Eats uber eats uber uber eats network white white St 21
@Fxngc	B-ORG
Network	I-ORG
network	O
huit	B-CARDINAL
uber	O
Eats	O
uber	O
eats	O
uber	O
uber	O
eats	O
network	O
white	O
white	O
St	O
21	O

#128
#@Squidsquirt @Aneeqah @JustVee1710 An Uber dashboard? That must have hurt
@Squidsquirt	O
@Aneeqah	O
@JustVee1710	O
An	O
Uber	O
dashboard	O
?	O
That	O
must	O
have	O
hurt	O

#129
#I honestly cancel nake plans that require me to drive, if I can't uber there or be fetched As'yeke!
I	O
honestly	O
cancel	O
nake	O
plans	O
that	O
require	O
me	O
to	O
drive	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
uber	O
there	O
or	O
be	O
fetched	O
As'yeke	B-PERSON
!	O

#130
#Fifa Black Friday promo should be good today, hopefully a lot of good Sbc’s and packs.
Fifa	B-ORG
Black	O
Friday	B-DATE
promo	O
should	O
be	O
good	O
today	B-DATE
,	O
hopefully	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
good	O
Sbc	B-ORG
’s	O
and	O
packs	O
.	O

#131
#@sonaldooooo @Ndombelefanboy The game is bad just like fifa this year...
@sonaldooooo	B-ORG
@Ndombelefanboy	O
The	O
game	O
is	O
bad	O
just	O
like	O
fifa	O
this	B-DATE
year	I-DATE
...	O

#132
#When my sister @karaBEYPS tells me she wants to buy Fifa for some guy https://t.co/4F0jJlJoAs
When	O
my	O
sister	O
@karaBEYPS	B-PERSON
tells	O
me	O
she	O
wants	O
to	O
buy	O
Fifa	B-ORG
for	O
some	O
guy	O
https://t.co/4F0jJlJoAs	O

#133
#Why do u need a lamp though? I want darkness when I sleep and I have LED lights when playing fifa to illuminate my room before I sleep
Why	O
do	O
u	O
need	O
a	O
lamp	O
though	O
?	O
I	O
want	O
darkness	O
when	O
I	O
sleep	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
LED	O
lights	O
when	O
playing	O
fifa	O
to	O
illuminate	O
my	O
room	O
before	O
I	O
sleep	O

#134
#Stadium check in World Cup run-up #FIFA #FridayThoughts Link : https://t.co/lyjOEPM2GA https://t.co/xLYReKSNRh
Stadium	O
check	O
in	O
World	B-EVENT
Cup	I-EVENT
run-up	O
\#	B-MONEY
FIFA	I-MONEY
\#	I-MONEY
FridayThoughts	O
Link	O
:	O
https://t.co/lyjOEPM2GA	O
https://t.co/xLYReKSNRh	O

#135
#@Chimabro @OgaNlaMedia eerienced fifa world cup coach - that is u20
@Chimabro	O
@OgaNlaMedia	B-ORG
eerienced	O
fifa	O
world	O
cup	O
coach	O
-	O
that	O
is	O
u20	O

#136
#@CarolRadull You mean our own Kasarani doesn't meet Fifa standards?
@CarolRadull	O
You	O
mean	O
our	O
own	O
Kasarani	B-PERSON
does	O
n't	O
meet	O
Fifa	B-ORG
standards	O
?	O

#137
#I'm now live playing FIFA 20 over on Mixer: https://t.co/iFQYZPGyCx ?
I	O
'm	O
now	O
live	O
playing	O
FIFA	O
20	B-CARDINAL
over	O
on	O
Mixer	B-PERSON
:	O
https://t.co/iFQYZPGyCx	O
?	O

#138
#MARATONA BLACK FRIDAY SU FIFA! | !fifapoints !offerte !bf !instantgaming !prime !sub | https://t.co/J4MCUGqMwb
MARATONA	O
BLACK	O
FRIDAY	O
SU	O
FIFA	O
!	O
|	O
!	O
fifapoints	O
!	O
offerte	B-PERSON
!	O
bf	B-PERSON
!	O
instantgaming	B-PERSON
!	O
prime	O
!	O
sub	O
|	B-PERSON
https://t.co/J4MCUGqMwb	I-PERSON

#139
#@Booboo67653746 @Joshua_Ubeku Statpads against Getafe? lol.. Someone scored 7 against Luxembourg and they are last on FIFA ranking but ok
@Booboo67653746	O
@Joshua_Ubeku	O
Statpads	B-PERSON
against	O
Getafe	B-ORG
?	O
lol	O
..	O
Someone	O
scored	O
7	B-CARDINAL
against	O
Luxembourg	B-GPE
and	O
they	O
are	O
last	O
on	O
FIFA	B-ORG
ranking	O
but	O
ok	O

#140
#Time to Fifa and smoke some pan and prepara for the weekend ahead 😤😤
Time	B-ORG
to	O
Fifa	B-ORG
and	O
smoke	O
some	O
pan	O
and	O
prepara	O
for	O
the	B-DATE
weekend	I-DATE
ahead	O
😤	B-GPE
😤	I-GPE

#141
#@Bradley_Mak2003 @roger_sent @ManUtd boy stop deluding like this is some FIFA/EA sports game you're playing this is not a quick fix
@Bradley_Mak2003	B-PERSON
@roger_sent	I-PERSON
@ManUtd	I-PERSON
boy	O
stop	O
deluding	O
like	O
this	O
is	O
some	O
FIFA	B-ORG
/	O
EA	O
sports	O
game	O
you	O
're	O
playing	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
quick	O
fix	O

